Chapter 498: Seizing a Pill

Several seconds of silence passed by, and everyone was staring at the living corpse, unsure of what was going to happen next.

However, even after a long wait, nothing happened, and the living corpse remained seated on the golden chair in a completely still manner.

"How could this be?" the elderly woman murmured to herself in incredulity as the excitement and anticipation in her eyes slowly faded.

Everyone heaved a collective sigh of relief upon seeing this, thinking that it was only a false alarm, while Feng Tiandu and Han Li returned their attention to the battle at hand.

However, right at this moment, a burst of gray light suddenly emerged from the living corpse's body, and it instantly spread forth like a spirit domain, sending gusts of fierce wind sweeping in all directions.

The elderly woman was instantly sent flying by the ferocious wind, crashing into a gray puppet with a loud thump.

The green pill cauldron also shuddered violently, and only after a burst of green light had flashed over its surface did it manage to stabilize itself again.

On top of that, the golden and gray puppets were swept off their feet by the tremendous force as well, and even the outermost layer of the sea of fire erupted outward before exploding violently.

The Vast Flow Palace cultivators hurriedly sprang back in retreat, but Daoist Hu Yan did the exact opposite, flipping a hand over to produce an antiquated oil lamp that was lit with a golden flame, then flew straight into the raging sea of fire.

It appeared that Yun Ni wasn't tipped off in advance, and an alarmed look appeared on her face as she yelled, "Hu Yan..."

Han Li immediately peered into the spirit domain with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, but he was unable to see anything aside from a vast expanse of gray mist.

Moments later, the gray mist slowly scattered, and Daoist Hu Yan shot out in a flash, then landed beside Yun Ni.

However, his clothes were in tatters, his entire body was charred black, and his beard had been entirely incinerated away.

Despite his sorry appearance, there was a smile on his face as he said to Yun Ni through voice transmission, "I managed to get one High Zenith Pill, but those golden puppets are too strong, so I didn't dare to try and get another one."

"Don't ever do that to me again!" Yun Ni scolded with a stern glare.

Once all of the dust had settled, the living corpse on the golden chair was revealed once again.

It was still seated in a completely still manner, and it seemed that nothing had changed, but the aura that it was giving off was already completely different.

In the blink of an eye, the two golden puppets appeared beside the chair, and one of them fed another High Zenith Pill into the living corpse's mouth, while the other puppet remained still on the spot with half of its body charred black and an arm missing.

After swallowing the second High Zenith Pill, a layer of light emerged over the living corpse's body, and its aura swelled even further.

At the same time, the two golden puppets joined the one that had delivered the first High Zenith Pill, and the three of them formed a protective encirclement around the living corpse.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, following which he took a glance at Daoist Hu Yan, just in time to see him remove the cloth pouch that he had been carrying this entire time from his back before lifting a corner of the pouch and quickly tossing the High Zenith Pill inside.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he immediately shot back in retreat as a streak of azure light, not wishing to prolong this battle against Feng Tiandu any further.

"You're not getting away!" Feng Tiandu roared in a furious voice, yet right as he was about to give chase, a pillar of blue light suddenly erupted into the heavens from behind him.

A tremendous aura was emanating from the pillar of blue light, causing the entire palace to tremble and sway.

At the center of the pillar of blue light was none other than Luo Qinghai.

At this moment, his entire body was basked in radiant blue light, and rippling blue radiance was surging out of his body, sweeping outward in all directions, while the chains around him were loosened significantly.

Feng Tiandu's expression darkened slightly, and he was forced to abandon his chase of Han Li to focus on Luo Qinghai, releasing a burst of black light from his sleeve to bolster the chains around him.

Out of all of the people here, Luo Qinghai posed the biggest threat to him, so he couldn't allow him to break free no matter what.

All of the chains instantly lit up, then began to squirm and constrict like living creatures.

"It's too late to try and restrain me now!" Luo Qinghai harrumphed coldly as he made a hand seal, and the pillar of blue light around him brightened even further, remaining still and resolute in the face of the constricting chains.

At the same time, he began chanting an incantation, and his lower body instantly transformed into a blue serpentine tail, while his upper body took on a half-human, half-snake appearance, while his aura also swelled drastically.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li appeared beside Daoist Hu Yan, and the latter gave him a grateful nod as he said, "Thank you for keeping Feng Tiandu occupied, Fellow Daoist Li."

Han Li merely gave a faint smile in response, and his gaze lingered for a moment on the yellow cloth pouch on Daoist Hu Yan's back, which was tightly sealed, making it impossible to see what was inside.

A curious look flashed through Han Li's eyes, but he didn't ask any questions as he turned his gaze toward Luo Qinghai, upon which he was quite startled by the sight of Luo Qinghai's new form.

A layer of translucent blue light surfaced over Luo Qinghai's body as he struggled with all his might, and he was quickly shedding the chains around him.

Feng Tiandu's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately swept a sleeve through the air, upon which dozens of thick black chains appeared around him.

The tips of these chains were extremely sharp, and they were giving off a cold black gleam, giving them the appearance of a series of black spears. There were also countless black runes dancing over the chains, giving off incredibly formidable law power fluctuations.

"Go!"

Feng Tiandu made a hand seal, and all of the black chains instantly shot forth like arrows out of crossbows, launching themselves at Luo Qinghai.

In response, Luo Qinghai flipped a hand over to produce a dark blue bead, which was giving off a formidable aura.

There appeared to be a tiny blue half-snake, half-humanoid figure sealed within the bead, but it couldn't be clearly seen due to excessively bright radiance that the bead was releasing.

A slightly pained look appeared in his eyes, but he still swallowed the bead without any hesitation, and in the next instant, the blue light radiating from his body began to flash erratically, while streams of dark blue light surged through his body.

Right at this moment, the oncoming black chains arrived, piercing through the pillar of blue light with ease before punching through Luo Qinghai's body as well.

In the blink of an eye, countless holes were stabbed into his body, but not even a single drop of blood flowed out, much to Feng Tiandu's surprise.

A cold sneer appeared on Luo Qinghai's face, and the blue light radiating from his body abruptly exploded outward as a series of ripples.

At the same time, an ancient incantation rang out, and it felt as if the language being used had existed since the beginning of time.

Feng Tiandu's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately switched to a different hand seal.

The black chains around him flashed with black light once again, then shot forth through the air, piercing through the blue ripples in a frenzy, but in complete futility.

Meanwhile, Luo Qinghai's chanting was becoming louder and louder, and pillars of blue water were shooting out of the surrounding space before fusing into the blue waves.

In the blink of an eye, a ball of blue water the size of a lake appeared, taking up close to half of the entire palace.

Light flashed at the center of the lake, and a ball of blue light emerged, containing a massive humanoid figure inside.

The figure was several hundred feet tall, and it had the upper body of an imposing middle-aged man wearing a loose-fitting blue robe that left his wide chest and sturdy shoulders exposed.

The man also had a long and curly blue beard that trailed all the way down to his chest.

However, the man's lower body was a thick blue serpentine tail that was coiled several times and at least 1,000 feet in length.

The man had a set of extremely authoritative facial features, giving him the appearance of an ancient water god, and he was also giving off a tremendous aura that surpassed the Golden Immortal Stage, keeping the surrounding black spirit domain at bay.

His aura has already reached the High Zenith Stage!

In the distance, Han Li and the others were all astonished to see this, and a hint of shock flashed through Feng Tiandu's eyes as well.

At this moment, Luo Qinghai was standing inside the projection of the giant blue man with radiant blue light glowing from his body, giving him a majestic and untouchable appearance.

All of a sudden, he raised a hand before casting an incantation seal, and the eyes of the giant blue man abruptly sprang open.

Arcs of blue lightning were flashing within his eyes as the blue man raised a hand of his own, upon which a blue staff appeared in his grasp.

The staff was glowing so radiantly that it was impossible to make out its exact shape, and the giant blue man lashed out with the staff at Feng Tiandu from afar.

A giant blue staff projection appeared, and there were countless arcs of blue lightning flashing over its surface, giving off a burst of devastating power.

In this instant, it was as if the staff were the only thing that existed between heaven and earth.

Even from outside the spirit domain, Han Li and the others could clearly sense the formidable aura of the staff, and they immediately darted back in retreat.

The giant staff projection appeared to be moving very slowly, but in the eyes of Feng Tiandu, who was directly facing the attack, it was moving at lightning speed, striking his black spirit domain without giving him any time to react.

His black spirit domain rippled violently before exploding, and all of the black chains inside the spirit domain were also snapped, freeing the elderly man from the Southern Dawn Race, the other Golden Immortal of the Blaze Dragon, and Nan Kemeng.

The three of them were ecstatic, and they immediately flew away in different directions.

After destroying the spirit domain, a significant amount of the staff projection's power seemed to have been expended, and it shrank down to just over half its original size, but it was still crashing down toward Feng Tiandu with unstoppable might.

Chapter 499: Confrontation

All of this had taken place over the span of just a few seconds, and Feng Tiandu let loose an involuntary muffled groan upon having his spirit domain destroyed, seemingly having suffered some severe internal injuries.

His expression changed drastically at the sight of the oncoming staff projection, and he shot back in retreat while making a frantic string of hand seals.

A black scroll flew out of his body, then unfurled itself to reveal that a lone, steep black mountain was painted upon it.

The scroll released countless rays of black light, while the black mountain that was depicted shuddered violently, then flew out of the scroll and rapidly swelled to over 1,000 feet with black mist swirling all around it.

The black mist around the mountain was filled with countless black runes that were giving off an incredibly heavy aura, and it was clear that this was a formidable treasure.

As soon as the black mountain appeared, the staff projection also arrived, and the black mist around the mountain was instantly scattered upon contact amid an earth-shattering boom.

In the instant that the two collided, a vast explosion of blue and black light instantly erupted in all directions, and the entire mountain shuddered violently.

Countless cracks began to appear on its surface, following which it exploded with tremendous force, sending countless loose rocks flying in all directions, while the black scroll was also torn into two.

However, the blue staff projection had also expended all of its power up to this point, and it flashed a few times before fading away.

Even though Feng Tiandu wasn't struck by the giant staff projection, he was still sent flying back several thousand feet by the shockwaves resulting from the clash, and a stunned look flashed through his eyes after he steadied himself.

Meanwhile, the projection of the giant blue figure rapidly shrank down before fading altogether to reveal Luo Qinghai.

At this point, he had already reverted back to his human form, and there were rings of incredibly dense blue light surging out of his body, but his complexion was extremely pale.

The four Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals and Nan Kemeng hurriedly flew over to his side before forming a protective encirclement around him.

"I'm fine," Luo Qinghai reassured as he flipped a hand over to produce a golden pill, which he promptly devoured.

An intrigued look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he noticed that the aura emanating from the pill was rather similar to that of the Golden Soul Pill.

A burst of golden light flashed over Luo Qinghai's face, and his complexion quickly returned to normal.

Meanwhile, the battle between Jin Tong and Qi Tianxiao was still raging, and a resounding clash took place between the two.

Jin Tong was sent flying by an eruption of gray light, while Qi Tianxiao was looking a little pale as he also shot back through the air as a streak of gray light.

As for Jin Tong, she was sent flying back several hundred feet, but she was completely unscathed, much to Qi Tianxiao's concern and dismay.

A furious roar erupted out of her mouth as she prepared to clash against Qi Tianxiao once again, but Han Li's voice suddenly rang out from beside her ears.

"Come back, Jin Tong."

Jin Tong hesitated momentarily, then made a series of threatening gestures at Qi Tianxiao before flying back to Han Li's side.

At this point, the Golden Immortal from the Blaze Dragon Dao had also arrived on the scene, and they were all gathered in a corner of the palace.

Meanwhile, Qi Tianxiao arrived by Feng Tiandu's side with a concerned expression, and the latter promptly devoured a black pill, upon which his complexion began to slowly recover.

At the same time, the elderly man from the Southern Dawn Race flew through the air as a streak of crimson light before landing beside the elderly woman.

With that, four distinct groups of cultivators were formed, and all of them were looking at one another, but none of them were in a hurry to make the first move.

Jin Tong flew back to Han Li's side before landing on his shoulder, then cast her gaze toward the two Golden Immortals from the Blaze Dragon Dao.

"When did these two show up? Are they good people? Are they strong?" Jin Tong asked.

A peculiar look flashed over the faces of both Golden Immortals upon hearing this.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he cast his gaze toward Daoist Hu Yan with an inquisitive look in his eyes.

This was something that he wanted to ask as well. It seemed that the two Golden Immortals were allies of theirs, but he didn't know whether that was confirmed to be the case.

"The situation was too chaotic earlier, so I wasn't able to explain everything to you, but Dao Lord Ouyang and I have actually already made an agreement some time ago to join forces in the immortal manor," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

"Fellow Daoist Li, I didn't think that you would already be at the Golden Immortal Stage. Congratulations," Ouyang Kuishan said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Han Li's mind was racing as he smiled and nodded in response. "You're far too kind, Dao Lord Ouyang. We were all part of the Blaze Dragon Dao at one point, so let's continue to work together from here onward."

Ouyang Kuishan and Daoist Hu Yan were both very pleased to see that Han Li was willing to accept this arrangement.

Han Li had shown himself capable of opposing Feng Tiandu on his own, and on top of that, he had a Golden Immortal Stage Gold Devouring Immortal on his side, so he was definitely a powerful ally.

With his cooperation, they now had a total of six Golden Immortals, making the most formidable camp present, and that was naturally going to be immensely beneficial for their plight in securing more High Zenith Pills.

"Having said that, there's something that I want to establish in advance," Han Li suddenly said.

"Please go ahead, Fellow Daoist Li," Daoist Hu Yan hurriedly prompted.

"We may all be working together right now, but the High Zenith Pills that each of us secure still go to ourselves, right?" Han Li asked.

Ouyang Kuishan's expression changed slightly upon seeing this.

However, before he had a chance to say anything, Daoist Hu Yan replied, "Of course. We're only joining forces to ward off the enemies present, but it's still up to ourselves to secure High Zenith Pills."

Ouyang Kuishan's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he exchanged a subtle glance with the other Blaze Dragon Dao Golden Immortal.

They were currently the two weakest cultivators in the group, so they had the worst chances of securing High Zenith Pills, but seeing as both Daoist Hu Yan and Han Li approved of this arrangement, they had no choice but to agree as well.

"Good," Han Li said as a faint smile appeared on his face, following which he turned his gaze back to the green pill cauldron.

He had already fulfilled his promise of helping Daoist Hu Yan secure a High Zenith Pill, so he no longer had any qualms.

Meanwhile, Luo Qinghai was also observing Han Li's group with a hint of wariness in his eyes.

At this point, only three of the nine High Zenith Pills had emerged, so there were still six left, and no one was in any hurry to strike.

The Dawn Fall Sect only had two people left, and Feng Tiandu had already displayed all of his trump cards. On top of that, he was undoubtedly severely taxed after that grueling battle, so he was no longer a cause for concern.

Instead, it was actually Han Li's camp that posed the biggest threat, given his time law domain and the Gold Devouring Immortal on his side.

Han Li and the others all bristled slightly at the sight of the rather unfriendly gaze that Luo Qinghai was directing their way.

Just now, Luo Qinghai had displayed High Zenith Stage power to break Feng Tiandu's spirit domain, and even though his aura had subsided since then, everyone was still quite wary of him.

"Be careful of Luo Qinghai, everyone. He possesses the bloodline of the true spirit Wa Serpent. [1] If I'm not mistaken, he must've devoured the true spirit core of a High Zenith Stage Wa Serpent just now, thereby allowing him to forcibly elevate his own cultivation base to the High Zenith Stage. Of course, in that form, he can't compare with a true High Zenith cultivator, but he's still not to be underestimated," Daoist Hu Yan informed Han Li and the others through voice transmission.

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon hearing this.

Han Li had once read some records pertaining to true spirit cores, so he knew that they were the origins of a true spirit being's bloodline.

Once a normal cultivator perished, it was very difficult for someone else to use their body of nascent soul, but this was different in the case of true spirit cores.

As long as one possessed the same bloodline, they would be able to use a true spirit core to unleash power far beyond their own. However, this was quite a risky move to make, and it was also very taxing on one's spiritual sense.

Han Li took a glance at Luo Qinghai, then asked through voice transmission, "Fellow Daoist Hu Yan, in your opinion, has Luo Qinghai completely exhausted the power of that true spirit core?"

"I don't think so. Given how cunning he is, I'm sure he wouldn't prematurely show his hand, so we have to be careful," Daoist Hu Yan warned in a solemn voice.

Everyone immediately nodded in response.

Han Li then took a glance at Feng Tiandu's duo before quickly shifting his gaze to the pair of Southern Dawn beings, upon which a peculiar look flashed through his eyes.

"Do you know those two, Fellow Daoist Li?" Daoist Hu Yan asked as he noticed the direction of Han Li's gaze.

"No," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

The pill that the elderly woman had brought out was most definitely an Origin Void Pill.

He had personally refined that pill, so there was no mistaking it.

However, at the time, he had given the pill to Wyrm 3, so how had it fallen into this woman's hands? Could it be that this was Wyrm 3 in disguise?

The only problem with that theory was that the cultivation base didn't seem to match up.

"We need to keep an eye on those two, especially that woman. She was able to avoid those stone statues just now with ease, but they don't seem to be interested in High Zenith Pills. It seems like their objective is that living corpse instead, and it's unclear what they're up to," Daoist Hu Yan mused in a rather perplexed manner.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this. That was exactly what he was wondering as well.

In fact, not only was the elderly woman interested in that living corpse, the same seemed to apply to Feng Tiandu as well.

The fact that it was situated in such an important place in the High Zenith Palace indicated that it was definitely no ordinary corpse, and the aura that had erupted out of its body after being fed that Origin Void Pill was also nothing to be scoffed at.

In contrast with the prior commotion, the palace was currently so silent that even the faintest of pin drops could be heard, and the atmosphere was rather oppressive, while the situation had also become quite murky.

Right at this moment, three of the dragons on the surface of the green pill cauldron lit up in unison with five-colored light, indicating that another three High Zenith Pills were about to take shape!

A vast expanse of golden light gathered in the sky above the golden palace once again, forming an enormous golden vortex that was significantly bigger than the two previous ones.

Everyone immediately turned their attention to the pill cauldron upon seeing this.

[1]. In Chinese mythology, the goddess of creation, Nüwa, is a half-human, half-snake being, and that's what "Wa Serpent" is referring to here.

[Back]

Chapter 500: Chaotic Battle

Han Li cast aside all of his errant thoughts as he focused his gaze intently on the green pill cauldron.

Three silver droplets emerged within the vortex, then fell upon the palace before exploding violently and crashing down as bolts of lightning.

Radiant golden light erupted out of the spirit patterns across the entire palace, forming a golden light barrier that kept the silver lightning at bay.

The golden and silver light clashed, releasing extremely formidable energy fluctuations that caused the entire palace to tremble violently.

However, no one was looking at the pill tribulation unfolding up above. Instead, all of them were staring intently at the pill cauldron, waiting for the next batch of pills to emerge.

Just like before, the silver light quickly subsided, while the golden light in the palace also gradually faded.

It didn't take long before both had completely faded, and yet another pill tribulation was successfully endured.

The three dragons on the pill cauldron opened their mouths, and three more High Zenith Pills shot out of the cauldron.

Immediately thereafter, three additional golden puppets emerged, seemingly from out of nowhere, then caught a High Zenith Pill each.

At the same time, everyone in the palace also rushed toward the three pills as quickly as they could.

Lights of different colors surfaced over their bodies before expanding outward to form a series of spirit domains.

At this point, everyone knew that it was time to display their true power, and eight or nine spirit domains of different colors had emerged within the palace in the blink of an eye.

All types of law powers were surging toward Han Li from all directions, instantly slowing him down significantly.

Everyone else was also slowed down by the multitude of spirit domains in the area, particularly Han Li's time spirit domain, which had the most significant slowing effect.

Han Li looked around momentarily, then abruptly slowed down so that he kept pace with everyone instead of darting ahead.

At the same time, all of the gray statues on either side of the palace also pounced forward once again.

However, they were also affected by all of the spirit domains in the area, and they were slowed down to an even greater extent than all of the cultivators present.

As for the golden array on the ground, it had just been destroyed by that eruption of gray light from the living corpse's body, so the white flame restriction wasn't triggered.

Even though everyone's speed was significantly diminished, the interior of the palace wasn't exactly a massive area, so everyone was still able to reach the three golden puppets in the blink of an eye.

Radiant golden light erupted out of the three puppets' bodies as they each threw a punch in a different direction, unleashing thick arcs of golden lightning that sprang forth in all directions.

The lightning attacks unleashed by these golden puppets were quite formidable, posing a threat even to Golden Immortals, but now that their attacks were scattered, they posed far less of a threat.

Hence, no one bothered to dodge the attacks as they briefly adopted some defensive measures before pouncing at the puppets to try and wrench the High Zenith Pills straight out of their hands.

Luo Qinghai harrumphed coldly as dazzling blue light erupted out of his body, and once again, his aura swelled to the High Zenith Stage.

The blue staff appeared in his hand amid a flash of blue light, and he swung it through the air, releasing a thick blade of blue light that tore through the oncoming arcs of golden lightning with ease before striking the right arm of one of the golden puppets.

A loud crack rang out as the puppet's arm was severed at the elbow, and the High Zenith Pill in its right hand was instantly sent flying through the air.

Daoist Hu Yan, Yun Ni, and the two Blaze Dragon Dao Golden Immortals just so happened to be nearby, and they immediately made a grab for the High Zenith Pill.

A cold look flashed through Luo Qinghai's eyes upon seeing this, and he swept his blue staff through the air once again, unleashing a thick staff projection that swept toward the four of them.

All four of them had witnessed the fearsome power of the staff projection, and they immediately shot back in retreat, not daring to stand their ground to try and secure the High Zenith Pill.

Luo Qinghai made no attempt to go after them, merely sweeping a sleeve through the air instead to release a burst of blue light that drew the High Zenith Pill into his grasp.

Even though Han Li was with Daoist Hu Yan and the others, he played no part in the brief fight over this first High Zenith Pill.

Instead, he abruptly sped up by severalfold, appearing beside the second High Zenith Pill in the blink of an eye before sweeping a sleeve through the air to release an azure flying sword that hurtled directly toward the puppet.

The golden puppet reacted extremely quickly, swinging around before throwing a punch at the azure flying sword.

Han Li harrumphed coldly as he made a hand seal, and a translucent golden thread shot out of the flying sword to strike the golden puppet.

A burst of translucent golden light erupted out of the golden thread to envelop the puppet, and it was instantly stopped cold in its tracks, following which the azure flying sword swept over its body.

Just like the other puppet, this one's arm was also severed, and a High Zenith Pill flew out of its grasp.

An ecstatic look emerged in Han Li's eyes as he immediately made a grab for the pill, but right at this moment, several dark red threads of light shot forth through the air from the side, and the elderly woman from the Southern Dawn Race was rushing in to stop Han Li.

At the same time, the elderly man also rushed at him while releasing two streaks of crimson light, which transformed into a pair of crimson skulls that hurtled toward Han Li from both the left and the right.

Instead of taking evasive measures, Han Li opened his mouth to release a burst of golden light, which contained several translucent golden threads, and the oncoming dark red threads were instantly stopped cold in their tracks.

The two bursts of formidable law powers clashed violently, causing the nearby space to tremble and rumble incessantly.

Han Li was rather surprised to see that these dark red threads were able to oppose his time law threads.

At the same time, Jin Tong shot forth through the air from his shoulder, rapidly swelling in size mid-flight before lashing out with its two front legs.

Several hundred streaks of translucent golden light were unleashed, forming a golden wave that swept up the two crimson skulls in the blink of an eye, and it didn't take long at all before they were destroyed.

Meanwhile, another golden figure emerged from Han Li's body amid a flash of golden light, and it was none other than Daoist Xie, which was holding a pair of Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The two swords instantly swelled to over 100 feet in length, and arcs of thick golden lightning flashed over their surface as they gave off a devastating aura.

Two giant streaks of golden sword qi shot forth with countless golden lightning runes surging over them, and they swept directly toward the pair of Southern Dawn beings.

The two of them were clearly caught off guard by Daoist Xie's abrupt emergence, and they didn't dare to directly withstand the two streaks of formidable sword qi, so they hurriedly took evasive measures.

Meanwhile, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light that swept up the High Zenith Pill before drawing it up his sleeve in the blink of an eye.

The elderly woman faltered slightly upon seeing this, then took a long glance at Han Li before darting back in retreat.

The dark red threads also disengaged themselves from their clash against Han Li's time law threads and flew back up her sleeve.

Right at this moment, Han Li's voice suddenly rang out beside the elderly woman's ears. "I didn't expect to see you here, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3."

Her expression stiffened ever so slightly upon seeing this, but she didn't slow down in the slightest as she continued flying back in retreat, as did the elderly man with her.

Han Li made a beckoning motion to draw his time law threads and Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords back to himself, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he watched the elderly woman fly away into the distance.

At this point, he was all but certain that she was indeed Wyrm 3.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom abruptly rang out nearby, followed by an eruption of black light.

Han Li turned to discover that all four Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals and Nan Kemeng had been sent flying through the air, while Feng Tiandu and Qi Tianxiao were standing not far away from them.

There was a cold sneer on Feng Tiandu's face as he held a High Zenith Pill in one hand, and two halves of a golden puppet were laying on the ground at their feet.

It had only been a few seconds since the three High Zenith Pills had emerged, and all three of them had already been claimed.

Meanwhile, the gray statues were heavily affected by all of the spirit domains in the area, so they were still yet to even reach the pill cauldron.

All of the gray puppets began to glow with radiant yellow light, which instantly connected together to form that giant go board projection again.

Individually, these puppets didn't pose much of a threat, but this go board projection ability that they were collectively able to unleash was extremely formidable, and everyone hurriedly flew back in retreat upon seeing this.

Han Li also did the same, releasing a burst of azure light out of his sleeve to sweep up Jin Tong before flying away himself, while Daoist Xie flew back into his body as a streak of golden light.

However, right at this moment, two black chains suddenly shot out the space behind him before wrapping themselves around his body, instantly stopping him cold in his tracks.

As a result, he was caught within the yellow go board projection, and he instantly felt as if there were an enormous mountain weighing down upon him.

He turned around with some difficulty to find Feng Tiandu watching him with a cold sneer on his face. Even as he was flying back in retreat, there were two black chains protruding out of his sleeve.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as radiant golden light erupted out of his body in all directions.

At the same time, a resplendent golden wheel appeared behind him.

Countless incredibly dense golden ripples surged through the air, spreading outward at an incredible speed, and both Feng Tiandu and Qi Tianxiao were instantly caught within them.

Immediately thereafter, both of them were stopped cold in their tracks, and it was as if they had been frozen on the spot.

Some of the nearby gray statues and close to half of the yellow go board projection were also encompassed within the golden ripples, and they were all slowed down to a crawl as well.

Luo Qinghai and the others were all astonished to see this, while Ouyang Kuishan exclaimed in incredulity, "Surely that's not the Mantra Treasured Axis!"

As a dao lord of the Blaze Dragon Dao, he was naturally aware of the Mantra Axis Scripture, but this Mantra Treasured Axis was unlike anything that they had ever seen or heard of before!

In particular, the hundreds of Time Dao Runes on the axis was simply mind-boggling to him!

Chapter 501: Soul Restoration

Out of everyone present, Daoist Hu Yan was the only one who remained composed in the wake of this revelation as he had already previously witnessed Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis.

Basked in the golden light, Han Li was able to fly out of the go board projection with ease, and he appeared beside Feng Tiandu's duo in the blink of an eye.

A hint of alarm and fear flashed through Feng Tiandu's eyes, and a layer of black light surfaced over his body, but it was only able to flash at an extremely low frequency as he fought with all his might to struggle free from the surrounding golden ripples.

A layer of gray light appeared over Qi Tianxiao's body as well, releasing a burst of corrosive law powers that began to eat away at the surrounding golden ripples.

However, these golden ripples were filled with bursts of incredibly formidable time law powers, and they remained completely unmoved in the face of the opposing law powers.

"Is that all you've got, Elder Feng? In that case, it's my turn!" Han Li declared in a cold voice, then casually swept a sleeve through the air.

Two streaks of azure light shot out of his sleeve, revealing themselves to be a pair of tiny azure swords, and they were able to pierce through the protective spiritual light around the bodies of Feng Tiandu's duo with ease before punching through their glabellas with a pair of dull thumps.

A walnut-sized hole appeared in each of their glabellas, but not even a single drop of blood flowed out. The two were still moving slowly along their original trajectories, but the light in their eyes was gradually fading.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he swept his sleeve through the air once again, releasing a burst of azure light that swept over the remains of the duo, drawing out their storage tools, the immortal treasures that they carried with them, and a pair of nascent souls before carrying them up his sleeve.

After that, he made a hand seal, and the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him vanished into his body at his behest.

The surrounding golden ripples also faded, and with that, everything was returned to normal.

Feng Tiandu and Qi Tianxiao's bodies fell onto the ground with a dull thud, and it seemed that they had been slain in the blink of an eye.

Not long ago, Feng Tiandu and Qi Tianxiao had been arguably the two most threatening figures out of everyone present, but all of a sudden, they had been reduced to a pair of corpses.

Everyone drew a collective sharp breath upon seeing this, and they all turned to Han Li with incredulity and wariness in their eyes.

Even Daoist Hu Yan was very much taken aback to see this, and he couldn't help but chuckle to himself in amusement.

Han Li took a glance at everyone else, and his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

Having just displayed his true power to so many people, this could certainly spell trouble for him in the future.

However, a sense of pride then welled up in his heart.

Back when he first entered the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, he was constantly being hunted by enemies more powerful than himself, so he was perpetually having to be cautious in everything that he did, not daring to let down his guard even for a moment in case he suffered the same fate as before.

However, now that he had reached the mid-Golden Immortal Stage and mastered the laws of time, he didn't need to fear any Golden Immortal cultivator. Furthermore, he had already devised a plan for what he was going to do once he left the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, so he didn't have to worry about these people.

After the golden ripples faded, Jin Tong was also able to move freely once again, and she glowered at the pair of bodies on the ground as she protested, "Why did you kill them, Uncle? I told you I wanted to kill them myself!"

"I gave you a chance already, but you weren't able to capitalize, so you can't blame me," Han Li replied with a wry smile, and before Jin Tong had a chance to reply, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that swept her up before flying toward the edge of the palace.

However, he had only just risen up into the air when he suddenly stopped in his tracks, then cast his gaze toward the green pill cauldron with a peculiar look in his eyes.

The cauldron had suddenly begun shaking again amid a loud rumbling sound, and the white flames beneath it suddenly reared up significantly, enveloping the entire bottom half of the cauldron.

An incredibly heated aura spread forth in all directions, causing the air temperature in the palace to spike drastically, and the surrounding space shimmered and warped, while the ground near the cauldron began to slowly melt.

The gray statues seemed to be quite fearful of these white flames, and they hurriedly sprang back in retreat. As a result, the yellow go board projection that they had released also faded.

At this point, everyone had gotten far away from the cauldron, and the gray statues had also flown back to their original spots on either side of the palace.

Everyone else in the distance was also quite shocked to see this, and all of their attention was immediately refocused on the cauldron.

The spirit patterns on the cauldron began to release bursts of green light, and the lid of the cauldron was trembling incessantly as thick pillars of white smoke erupted forth in all directions.

Dull, thunderous rumbling was also ringing out within the cauldron, but it was quickly able to stabilize itself again.

Immediately thereafter, a loud ringing sound rang out from within the cauldron, and the remaining three dragons began to glow with radiant five-colored light, indicating that more pills were about to take shape, much to everyone's elation and befuddlement.

Prior to this, the release of each batch of pills had been punctuated by a cooldown interval, but on this occasion, the last three pills had only just emerged a moment ago, yet the final three pills were already about to take shape.

However, everyone then quickly realized that this could be explained by that sudden eruption of white flames from beneath the cauldron.

Abruptly fanning the flames during the pill refinement process could indeed accelerate the formation of the pill, but it was an extremely risky maneuver that could easily result in the pills being ruined altogether.

The world's origin qi above the palace began to churn once again, and countless golden clouds converged to form an enormous vortex.

Three bursts of silver light descended out of the vortex before striking the roof of the palace with tremendous force, and once again, the same clash of golden and silver light began to unfold.

A few seconds later, a dull thump rang out in the sky, and all of the silver light faded away, as did the golden light within the palace.

Immediately thereafter, everyone pounced at the cauldron again, but this time, they didn't get too close.

At this point, everyone had already gained some experience, and they had determined how far a distance they had to maintain from the cauldron in order to avoid triggering the gray statues.

Before long, the three dragons on the pill cauldron began to glow even more radiantly, following which a High Zenith Pill flew out of each of their mouths.

Everyone immediately converged toward the pill cauldron once again, and just like before, a multitude of spirit domains were summoned to encompass the entire palace.

Even though Han Li had already secured two High Zenith Pills up to this point, it certainly couldn't hurt to have more, and he was just about to rush at the cauldron as well when a burst of gray light suddenly shot out of his body before hurtling toward the cauldron.

The gray light contained the Soul Nurturing Burner that the soul fragment was housed in, but the talismans adhered to the burner had already become dull and devoid of luster, clearly having been rendered ineffective.

Han Li was very much taken aback to see this, and he hurriedly swept a hand through the air, conjuring a giant golden palm projection that made a grab for the streak of gray light, but all it managed to catch was an afterimage.

The streak of gray light was astonishingly fast, reaching the cauldron in the blink of an eye as if through instantaneous teleportation, and it seemed to have been completely unaffected by all of the spirit domains in the area.

The streak of gray light swept up the three High Zenith Pills like lightning, then continued to fly onward, appearing above the golden chair just an instant later.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and everyone immediately stopped cold in their tracks with stunned looks on their faces.

Immediately thereafter, the Soul Nurturing Burner abruptly exploded, and the soul fragment drifted out from within.

"I knew I could count on you, kid!" the soul fragment chortled with glee as it took a glance at Han Li, then flew into the body of the living corpse seated on the golden chair, taking the three High Zenith Pills with it.

All of a sudden, nine golden stone pillars erupted out of the ground near the chair, and a burst of golden light rose up from the stone pillars to form a thick golden light barrier that encompassed the chair and the living corpse within.

Bursts of golden light were flashing over the light barrier, giving it an indestructible appearance, while a layer of rippling gray light emerged over the living corpse's body.

Even through the golden light barrier, everyone could clearly sense a burst of vitality rising up within the living corpse.

Right at this moment, two figures arrived on the scene, then landed beside the golden chair. It was the two Southern Dawn Race Golden Immortals, and both of them had excited looks on their faces.

All of a sudden, three golden puppets appeared to stand in the way of the two Golden Immortals, and they each threw a punch, sending three thick bolts of golden lightning hurtling toward the duo.

"Piss off!" the elderly woman yelled as a flurry of dark red law threads shot forth, then converged to form a dark red blade of light that swept through the air while giving off a burst of tremendous law power fluctuations.

Han Li's pupils immediately contracted slightly upon seeing this.

He could sense that this burst of law powers wasn't inferior to his time law powers.

The dark red blade of light abruptly sped up, flying through the bodies of the three golden puppets as a dark red shadow, and the three bolts of golden lightning shuddered momentarily before exploding violently.

The three puppets were also stopped cold in their tracks before splitting apart at the waist and falling to the ground in a lifeless fashion.

The dark red blade of light continued onward without pause, striking the golden light barrier with tremendous force, causing the light barrier to ripple violently, while the entire palace also shuddered.

However, just a moment later, the golden light barrier fell still again.

Chapter 502: Arrival

The elderly woman took a glance at the golden light barrier, and a hint of elation and approval flashed through her eyes.

The elderly man didn't say anything, but his gaze was firmly focused on the living corpse inside the golden light barrier, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

All of a sudden, Luo Qinghai flew through the air before also descending in front of the golden light barrier.

"What are you trying to do, Grand Palace Master Luo?" the elderly man asked in a cold voice.

"What am I trying to do? Most of the High Zenith Pills are in that thing's body right now! Are you trying to claim all of those pills for yourselves?" Luo Qinghai sneered as he began to chant an incantation, and a burst of radiant blue light appeared over his body.

The elderly man's expression darkened slightly, and he was just about to do something when the elderly woman raised a hand to stop him.

"It's fine, let him do as he pleases."

The elderly man's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he still did as he was told in the end.

A layer of fiery blue light appeared over Luo Qinghai's body, and he began to give off an enormous High Zenith Stage as he swept a sleeve through the air.

The blue staff projection appeared once again, and it was giving off a terrifying aura as it struck the golden light barrier.

The entire palace shuddered violently, as did the golden light barrier, but once again, it was able to remain firm.

Luo Qinghai's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and everyone else was also quite stunned by how resilient the light barrier was proving to be.

All of a sudden, the entire palace had fallen silent, and the only sound came from the scorching white flame beneath the pill cauldron.

"What's the deal with that soul fragment in that Soul Nurturing Burner, Fellow Daoist Li?" Daoist Hu Yan asked as he made his way over to Han Li.

Everyone else was also quite interested to hear the answer to this question, and all of a sudden, everyone's attention was focused on Han Li again.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then explained, "I discovered the burner in a set of ruins, and I thought it was rather special, so I decided to take it with me. I didn't know there was a soul fragment residing in it."

This was clearly not the truth, but Daoist Hu Yan merely nodded in response and didn't ask any further questions.

As for everyone else, they were clearly also unconvinced, but just like Daoist Hu Yan, no one raised any further questions.

Luo Qinghai returned his gaze to the golden light barrier, then suddenly gave a cold harrumph before walking away.

The other Vast Flow Palace cultivators hurriedly approached him, and they began to converse with one another through voice transmission.

Meanwhile, Han Li was staring at the living corpse inside the golden light barrier with a contemplative look on his face.

How exactly were that soul fragment and the living corpse related? Had the soul fragment asked him to take it out of that secret area so that it could come here?

Also, Wyrm 3 had requested him to refine this Origin Void Pill well in advance, so was she already aware that this living corpse was inside the High Zenith Palace? If so, what was her objective?

All of these questions were flashing through his mind, but he didn't have answers for any of them.

In the end, he merely shook his head and refrained from pondering these matters any further.

It wasn't like they had anything to do with him anyway. As long as Wyrm 3 and the others didn't do anything to directly harm his interests, he had no intention of getting involved in their affairs.

Most importantly, all of the High Zenith Pills had already emerged from the cauldron at this point, and he had managed to secure two of them, thereby completing his objective, so he didn't want to stay here any longer.

With that in mind, he was just about to turn around when he suddenly cast his gaze toward the living corpse under the light barrier as a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes.

Just now, one of the living corpse's fingers seemed to have twitched slightly.

However, it was only for an instant, and he couldn't be sure that it wasn't just a figment of his imagination.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Li?" Daoist Hu Yan asked through voice transmission.

Han Li took a glance at everyone else to discover that no one else seemed to have noticed what he had just seen, and he shook his head as he replied, "Nothing."

Daoist Hu Yan didn't pursue the subject any further, instead changing the topic as he suggested, "It doesn't appear as if there are any other treasures in this palace, so how about we go somewhere else?"

Han Li immediately cast his gaze toward the roof of the palace and all of the surrounding restrictions upon hearing this.

The combination of the palace's roof and these restrictions was able to ward off pill tribulations, and as a dao pill master, he was naturally very intrigued.

However, having just unleashed his spirit domain, he had already determined that the roof of the palace was one with the rest of the palace.

Even after such a fierce battle had taken place, the walls of the palace were still completely unscathed, indicating that the entire structure was near indestructible, so it was clearly impossible to remove the roof and take it with him.

With that in mind, Han Li heaved a forlorn internal sigh as he nodded in response.

Aside from the High Zenith Pills, he had reaped some other rewards as well. Having witnessed the golden palace withstand four pill tribulations, he had gleaned much of the profound elements of the restrictions set up within the palace, and there were some similarities between these restrictions and his Integrated Five Extremes Mountain.

"Have you recorded everything?" Han Li asked internally.

Somewhere inside his body, Daoist Xie was holding a white jade slip, which contained an extremely complete and detailed image of all of the restrictions in the entire palace, and it gave an affirmative response.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon receiving this confirmation.

The restrictions in this place were quite profound, and he was planning to study them carefully once he left the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor. If he could incorporate this set of restrictions into his Integrated Five Extremes Mountain, the result may not be inferior to this golden roof, and that would surely be immensely helpful to his future pill refinement.

Right at this moment, a loud crack suddenly rang out from the green pill cauldron, and Han Li turned to discover that Jin Tong had flown onto the cauldron in her beetle form.

He had completely failed to notice this, and at this moment, she was taking large bites out of the cauldron.

The white flame beneath the cauldron had already receded, and a layer of green light appeared over its surface in an attempt to keep Jin Tong at bay, but to no avail.

Perhaps it was because the white flames had just incinerated the restrictions around the cauldron, but on this occasion, the gray statues on either side of the palace remained completely still.

"What are you doing, Jin Tong?" Han Li flew over to the cauldron in a flash, and a pained look flashed through his eyes at the sight of the chunk that had already been bitten out of it.

Jin Tong was chewing on that chunk of the cauldron as she replied in a muffled voice, "I'm starving after so much exercise! I've had to hold myself back this entire time because you told me to wait until all of the pills were ready!"

"Fine, but there's no time for you to eat the cauldron now," Han Li replied with a resigned sigh, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that enveloped the entire cauldron.

Regardless of how exceptional the cauldron was, there was no changing the fact that a chunk had already been bitten out of it, and there was no point in scolding Jin Tong. Furthermore, he didn't possess the ability to repair a treasure of such a high caliber, so it would just have to serve as a snack for Jin Tong later.

Everyone else took a glance in Han Li's direction, then quickly averted their eyes.

All of the High Zenith Pills had already emerged, while the cauldron itself had already been damaged, thereby significantly lowering its value, so it wasn't worth fighting for, particularly if it meant having to oppose a Golden Immortal who had mastered the laws of time.

With another sweep of Han Li's sleeve, the burst of azure light raised the cauldron upward, and the entire palace shuddered violently as the cauldron's deep-rooted legs were forcibly wrenched out of the ground.

The residual green light flashing over its surface instantly faded, and Han Li stowed both Jin Tong and the cauldron away into a spirit beast pouch.

In the same instant that the cauldron flew into the spirit beast pouch, a white shadow shot out from within, then vanished into Han Li's body in the blink of an eye.

Daoist Xie was currently seated with its legs crossed somewhere in Han Li's body, and a burst of white light suddenly flashed nearby, then transformed into none other than the Flame of Essence.

At this moment, the Flame of Essence was in its humanoid form, and not only had it grown up significantly, its facial features had become even more detailed and intricate.

Most importantly, the aura that it was giving off was several times more formidable than before, and waves of scorching heat were sweeping out of the white flames around its body.

Daoist Xie opened his eyes, and its brows furrowed slightly as it distanced itself slightly from the tiny fiery figure.

The Flame of Essence opened its mouth, and a High Zenith Pill flew out from within.

However, this pill was different from the other High Zenith Pills in that it was riddled with a series of silver patterns, which formed the visage of a three-legged golden crow, and it was also giving off a far more formidable aura than the other pills.

The tiny fiery figure tossed the High Zenith Pill upward, and it vanished into thin air amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

Inside the palace, a barely detectable hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes as he made his way toward Daoist Hu Yan and the others.

Right at this moment, two streaks of light suddenly descended from above, then faded to reveal a pair of figures.

They were none other than Xue Ying and Gongshu Jiu, and as soon as they arrived in the palace, they immediately took in the chaotic scenes around them.

Everyone's attention was instantly drawn to the duo, and a benevolent smile appeared on Gongshu Jiu's face as he remarked, "Well, well, well, it looks like there's quite a bit going on here."

His voice wasn't very loud, but it was clearly audible to everyone inside the palace.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of Gongshu Jiu. He didn't know who this man was, but a sense of foreboding had welled up in his heart nonetheless as he was completely unable to glean the man's cultivation base.

Meanwhile, Luo Qinghai was observing Xue Ying with his brows furrowed slightly in befuddlement.

Gongshu Jiu swept his gaze across everyone in the hall, and his smile grew even wider as he mused, "Looks like it's my lucky day today! Not only have I run into so many Reincarnation Palace cultivators in one place, there are quite a few big fish among you! I really did make the right decision to come here."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a near-transparent light barrier slowly unfurled around him, instantly enveloping the entire golden palace.

Chapter 503: Too Late

Enveloped within Gongshu Jiu's spirit domain, everyone hurriedly began to inspect the changes that had taken place in themselves and the environment around them.

Han Li was holding tightly onto his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, and thin arcs of lightning were dancing over its surface. He discovered that the semi-transparent spirit domain wasn't giving off any energy fluctuations, as if it almost didn't exist, and that only made him feel even more uneasy.

Xue Ying took a step forward, then looked down at everyone in the palace with a haughty expression as she declared, "Esteemed Immortal Envoy Gongshu of the Heavenly Court is here, come and pay your respects!"

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon hearing this.

The title of "immortal envoy" meant that not only was this person an important figure in the Heavenly Court, it also indicated that he had to be at least an early-High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal.

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni exchanged a wary glance upon hearing this, while the pair of Southern Dawn Race Golden Immortals were also looking on with tightly furrowed brows.

As for Han Li, he immediately recalled the True Immortal by the name of He Kang that he had encountered while opposing the Stemborer Queen back in the Spirit Realm. He Kang had proclaimed himself to be an immortal emissary, and that he was under the direct command of an immortal envoy.

It was also from He Kang that Han Li found out for the first time that the Spirit Refinement Technique was a forbidden technique in the Immortal Realm, and that anyone who cultivated it would be hunted down by immortal envoys and emissaries.

After some hesitation, Luo Qinghai slowly strode over to Gongshu Jiu, then extended a respectful bow as he greeted, "Luo Qinghai of the Vast Flow Palace pays his respects to the esteemed immortal envoy."

"Grand Palace Master Luo, your Vast Flow Palace has been causing quite a bit of trouble for our Northern Glacial Immortal Palace over the years," Gongshu Jiu remarked with a smile.

Luo Qinghai was completely unfazed as he continued in a respectful manner, "Our Vast Flow Palace has always followed the rules stipulated by the Heavenly Court, and we've never gotten ourselves involved with evil forces like the Reincarnation Palace. Seeing as you've come here to eradicate these Reincarnation Palace cultivators, all of us will leave now so we won't get in your way."

He gave Nan Kemeng and the others a nod as he spoke, gesturing for them to leave.

However, right at this moment, a glimmer of golden light suddenly flashed over the semi-transparent light barrier, and the entire spirit domain began to give off bursts of formidable law power fluctuations.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, and it felt to him as if all of the world's origin qi had been completely frozen and immobilized.

"What is the meaning of this, esteemed immortal envoy?" Luo Qinghai asked.

"No one is allowed to leave until I've made sense of the situation here," Gongshu Jiu replied.

"Luo Qinghai! You deceived us and trapped us in that lake, and now, you've collaborated with these Reincarnation Disciple scoundrels to kill Palace Master Xiao! I bet you're already a member of the Reincarnation Palace yourself!" Xue Ying accused.

A wry smile appeared on Luo Qinghai's face as he argued, "That's not the case, Deputy Palace Master Xue. Back at the lake, I could tell that the restriction you were trapped in was quite formidable, so I decided to turn back to find Palace Master Xiao so that we could save you together.

“Unfortunately, I was delayed by the events here, and that's why I wasn't able to make it back to you. As for Palace Master Xiao, I swear on my life that I harbored no animosity toward him,and I certainly had no intention of harming him. Speaking of which, did something happen to him? I didn't see him at all on the way here."

He swept his gaze subtly over a few of the other figures in the palace as he spoke, clearly trying to shift the blame onto others.

A furious look appeared on Xue Ying's face, and she was just about to say something else, only to be stopped by Gongshu Jiu.

"Over the years, Xiao Jinhan has always been plotting to unite the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region, while our Heavenly Court has always been against the idea. However, he refused to listen to orders, and now that he's perished, I suppose I can only say that he's fallen onto his own sword," Gongshu Jiu said.

Luo Qinghai feigned a shocked expression as he exclaimed, "What? Palace Master Xiao has passed away?"

Gongshu Jiu paid no heed to him as he continued, "Having said that, it seems like his actions have inadvertently led to a good outcome for me."

At the same time, a burst of tremendous, invisible force suddenly descended upon everyone in the hall from all directions, and they hurriedly released their own spirit domains to protect themselves.

Han Li and the others were all gathered together, and their spirit domains were stacked on top of one another in an attempt to ward off this immense pressure, but the effects were virtually negligible.

"What kind of law power is this?" Ouyang Kuishan asked as a faint sheen of sweat began to appear on his forehead.

"It seems to be some type of qi laws, and this man's mastery over law powers is superior even to Feng Tiandu," Daoist Hu Yan mused with a grim expression.

Meanwhile, Han Li remained silent, but his mind was racing, and he was already contemplating how to make an escape. However, he had to wait for the right opportunity to present itself.

It seemed that the sense of foreboding that he had felt earlier was warranted. In hindsight, with so many important figures of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region clashing in one place, it was almost inevitable that a transcendent figure would arrive to oversee proceedings.

Given his current mid-Golden Immortal Stage cultivation base and his mastery over the laws of time, he was virtually invincible among Golden Immortals, but he still couldn't oppose a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal.

Ultimately, he could only blame himself for staying too long.

As a True Immortal, Nan Kemeng was naturally faring even worse than all of the Golden Immortals in the palace.

Even though he was situated in Luo Qinghai's spirit domain, he was still struck by a sense of asphyxiation and excruciating pain all over his entire body. His ears were also buzzing so loudly that he was barely even able to hear anything else.

Luo Qinghai could see the terrible condition that his beloved disciple was in, and he was finally unable to suppress his temper any longer as he made a grabbing motion with both hands, instantly conjuring up a massive vortex of blue light that devoured Gongshu Jiu in the blink of an eye.

A series of indistinct water dragons were surging through the vortex, which was constantly shrinking in size, compressing toward the center with tremendous force as if it were attempting to pulverize whoever was trapped inside.

However, there seemed to be an invisible wall of qi between Gongshu Jiu and the wavy vortex, and no matter how much pressure the vortex exerted upon the wall of qi, it was unable to break through.

Luo Qinghai wasn't surprised to see this, and he continued to constrict the vortex even further while giving a nod to the other Vast Flow Palace cultivators.

Having just forcibly elevated himself to the High Zenith Stage, he was currently severely taxed, so even just trapping Gongshu Jiu on a temporary basis was proving to be a struggle for him.

The four Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals immediately sprang into action, positioning themselves around Luo Qinghai and Nan Kemeng before each of them summoned a jade badge.

A collective incantation rang out as the images of the ancient sea beasts on the badges began to glow radiantly, with each of them releasing a burst of blue light that connected together to form a square array.

Before long, the complexions of the four Golden Immortals had turned very pale, clearly indicating that they were under immense strain, and a series of extremely complex patterns began to appear on the ground, giving off formidable spatial fluctuations.

"I heard that in the past, four separate arrays had to be set up in order to unleash the Four Seas Roaming Array, yet to think that you're able to accomplish the same thing with just a set of four jade badges. How impressive, Grand Palace Master Luo," Gongshu Jiu remarked from within the wavy vortex with a hint of approval in his voice.

Luo Qinghai offered no response as he began to make a rapid string of hand seals.

The four Golden Immortals had indeed just unleashed the Four Seas Roaming Array, but it was only a simplified version, so it naturally couldn't compare with the original, but it would still be enough to help them escape from this place.

The patterns on the ground at the center of the array were becoming brighter and brighter, while the spatial fluctuations emanating from within were also becoming more and more formidable.

However, right as the array was about to be activated, the wavy vortex suddenly exploded.

A layer of chaotic white qi had appeared around Gongshu Jiu, and it was only about three inches away from his body, but it was raging like a ferocious storm and seemed to contain tremendous power.

"Didn't I just say that no one is allowed to leave until I've had a chance to make sense of the situation here?" Gongshu Jiu asked, and even though the smile on his face remained unchanged, all of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators felt chills run down their spines at the sight of it.

Immediately thereafter, Gongshu Jiu reached out with one hand before clenching it into a tight fist, and four loud thumps rang out in succession as the badges in the hands of the four Golden Immortals exploded on after the other.

As a result, the array also exploded before scattering in all directions as countless specks of blue light.

The four Golden Immortals threw up a mouthful of blood in unison, and two of them collapsed to the ground.

The fair-skinned scholar hurriedly flipped a hand over to produce a pair of pills, which he fed to the collapsed Golden Immortals.

Inside Gongshu Jiu's spirit domain, the world's origin qi had completely ceased flowing, and no one was able to draw upon the world's origin qi outside the spirit domain to replenish their immortal spiritual power reserves, so they could only do so by using pills and Immortal Origin Stones.

Gongshu Jiu took a glance at Luo Qinghai, and a hint of derision flashed through his eyes as he began to make his way toward Han Li.

While passing by the Vast Flow Palace cultivators, everyone saw a patch of space suddenly warp and twist, following which the two collapsed Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals were crushed into the ground, instantly reduced to two piles of mangled flesh and bones.

Two blue nascent souls flew out of their remains, then rushed toward Luo Qinghai in a blind panic, but they weren't able to get very far before they were caught by a burst of qi and dragged up Gongshu Jiu's sleeve.

Luo Qinghai became even more furious upon seeing this, but in the end, he could only look on with tightly clenched fists.

Chapter 504: Joining Forces

"Chi Lijiao, Daoist Hu Yan, Wyrm 3... The three of you have committed quite a few transgressions, particularly you," Gongshu Jiu said as he stopped in his tracks and pointed a finger at the elderly woman from the Southern Dawn Race.

A perplexed look flashed through Daoist Hu Yan's eyes as he cast his gaze toward the elderly woman.

It was clear that he had heard of Wyrm 3 before, but was unaware that the elderly woman was Wyrm 3 in disguise.

Wyrm 3's expression stiffened slightly, but there wasn't much fear in her eyes as she looked back at Gongshu Jiu. However, the same couldn't be said for the elderly man beside her.

Meanwhile, Yun Ni turned to Daoist Hu Yan with a concerned look in her eyes.

"I've been looking everywhere for you three, but the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor had gathered all of you in one place. This is fantastic! It'll certainly save me a great deal of trouble," Gongshu Jiu continued as his smile widened even further.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he suddenly raised an eyebrow as his gaze fell upon the living corpses seated on the golden chair.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately yelled, "Everyone, all of us have played a hand in Xiao Jinhan's demise, so we're now in complete opposition against the Immortal Palace! This immortal envoy has clearly trapped all of us in his spirit domain with the intention of killing us all, so the only chance that we have at survival is to work together!"

Gongshu Jiu's attention was drawn to Han Li upon hearing this, but he merely watched Han Li with a smile, making no intention to stop him, as if what Han Li was saying had nothing to do with him.

A wry smile appeared on Luo Qinghai's face upon hearing this. In the wake of Han Li's declaration, his involvement in Xiao Jinhan's demise was virtually set in stone. Even though he wasn't actually a direct participant, Gongshu Jiu was certainly not going to believe that.

However, he wasn't overly bothered by this. Han Li was correct in saying that Gongshu Jiu clearly harbored intentions of killing everyone in the palace, so he had no choice but to work with everyone else anyway.

In that case, there was nothing for him to hesitate about. If he could somehow survive this ordeal, then he would just have to lead the Vast Flow Palace to defect to the Reincarnation Palace, which had already tried to recruit the Vast Flow Palace on many past occasions.

"Take this, Meng'er, it'll help you better withstand his spirit domain. I may not be able to look after you once the battle begins," Luo Qinghai said to Nan Kemeng as he handed the latter a longan-sized blue bead.

He then taught him a mantra for a secret technique through voice transmission.

Nan Kemeng's complexion was still very pale, but he reassured, "Don't worry, Master, I'll be fine."

He then accepted the blue bead and promptly swallowed it, then began to chant an incantation, upon which a layer of gentle blue light emerged over his lower abdomen, then swelled to form a blue light barrier with a radius of around 10 feet to encompass his entire body.

Nan Kemeng instantly felt as if he had been enveloped in a layer of gentle force that alleviated much of the crushing pressure and sense of asphyxiation that were weighing down upon him.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

That's a Profound Heavenly Spirit Domain!

Luo Qinghai had used a Profound Heavenly Treasure to help Nan Kemeng conjure up a faux spirit domain to ward off the power of Gongshu Jiu's spirit domain.

The fact that he was doing this indicated that he had already decided to accept Han Li's proposal.

Just like Luo Qinghai, everyone else had also realized that the only chance at survival that they had was to work together, and thus, all of them positioned themselves around Gongshu Jiu and Xue Ying, trapping them in an encirclement.

"What do you all think you're doing? How dare you display such blatant disrespect to Immortal Envoy Gongshu? Are you trying to oppose the Heavenly Court?"

Despite the brave front that Xue Ying was putting up, she unconsciously sidled up a little closer to Gongshu Jiu, and it was clear that she was feeling the pressure.

"Looks like all of you think that you can beat me thanks to your numbers advantage, but if that really were the case, then why would anyone bother to cultivate? How unfortunate. I wonder how long it'll take the Northern Glacial Immortal Region to recover after today," Gongshu Jiu lamented as he shook his head with a forlorn expression.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a sharp ringing sound suddenly rang out in the surrounding space.

Everyone in the palace was instantly struck by a burst of sharp pain in their eardrums, while the tremendous pressure surging toward them from all directions became several times more formidable.

Luo Qinghai immediately sprang into action, making a hand seal to conjure up a ball of blue light, which rapidly swelled in size to encompass everyone within it like a turbulent wave.

After being encompassed within the blue light barrier, the pressure on everyone was instantly lessened somewhat.

"Looks like you've made some decent progress in mastering the laws of the sea. Your crimes aren't all that severe, and I was originally only planning to make you serve as an immortal servant for a million years as a punishment, but you've insisted on digging your own grave," Gongshu Jiu remarked with a forlorn expression.

Daoist Hu Yan and the others also quickly followed suit, and light barriers of different colors emerged one after the other to encompass the entire palace, while different types of law power fluctuations surged toward Gongshu Jiu and Xue Ying.

However, Han Li had refrained from revealing his time spirit domain this entire time. His time law powers had been severely taxed during the prior battle, and while he hadn't completely run out, he also couldn't afford to use it without discretion.

In the face of a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal, he had to be extremely meticulous, using every single ounce of his law powers where they would truly make a difference.

Gongshu Jiu was instantly inundated by a multitude of spirit domains, but his expression remained completely unchanged.

He casually swept a sleeve through the air, and two bursts of golden light emerged to form a pair of halberd-wielding puppets that were clad in golden armor.

As soon as the pair of puppets emerged, golden light that was filled with incredibly abundant metal law power fluctuations erupted out of their bodies, and their auras were comparable to those of late-Golden Immortal cultivators.

"Go!" Gongshu Jiu ordered, and the pair of golden-armored puppets instantly charged at Daoist Hu Yan and Luo Qinghai.

"Leave this puppet to us, Palace Master," the fair-skinned scholar said as he and the other Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortal charged at the oncoming golden-armored puppet.

Meanwhile, Ouyang Kuishan and the other dao lord had stepped forward to oppose the other puppet, while Yun Ni began drifting toward Xue Ying.

A hint of concern flashed through Daoist Hu Yan's eyes upon seeing this. Yun Ni had already sustained injuries while rescuing him earlier, so she was not in prime condition.

However, given the current situation, he couldn't afford to get distracted. After all, Gongshu Jiu was a bona fide High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal, and even with Han Li, Wyrm 3, Chi Lijiao, and Luo Qinghai on his side, their chances of victory were probably still slim to none.

"At this point, there's no use in thinking about anything else. Only by giving it our all will we have any chance at survival," Han Li declared through voice transmission.

"Your time law powers are extremely formidable, Fellow Daoist Li, so we'll need you to make some significant contributions when it counts," Luo Qinghai said in a grim voice.

"I'll be sure to do my best, and similarly, I hope that you'll also unleash your full power. As the sect master of the Vast Flow Palace, I'm sure you have some more tricks up your sleeve," Han Li replied.

Luo Qinghai offered no response to this, and at the same time, Gongshu Jiu was already making his first move.

He began making a string of complex hand seals, and bursts of viscous mist that were of a milky white color emerged behind Han Li and the others, then took on the form of a series of misty humanoid figures.

Everyone's expressions changed drastically upon seeing this.

As it turned out, the outlines of these misty figures were identical to theirs, and it was as if they were their shadows. What was even more astonishing to them was that the auras of these misty figures were also extremely similar to their own.

"Are these domain spirits?" Daoist Hu Yan mused with tightly furrowed brows.

It was said that once one's spirit domain reached the late-Spiritform Stage, it would be capable of conjuring up domain spirits similar to living beings, and these domain spirits were similar in nature to puppets and Dao Warriors, while their powers depended on the cultivation base and law powers of the owner of the spirit domain.

"I don't think so," Luo Qinghai replied. "If these were spirit domains, then they wouldn't be so similar to us. I think this is another ability of his qi law powers."

Before they had a chance to speculate any further on this matter, the misty figures were already charging at them.

Daoist Hu Yan raised the longsword in his hand, and crimson flames were revolving around its blade as he slashed it horizontally toward the oncoming misty figure.

A burst of crimson light emerged around the misty figure as well, and scorching flames rose up over its entire body as it also summoned a fiery longsword before slashing it through the air.

The two fiery swords clashed with a resounding boom, and a wall of fire rose up between Daoist Hu Yan and the misty figure.

The two of them then flew through the wall of fire in unison before their swords clashed once again.

On the other side, the misty figure that was facing Luo Qinghai had turned into a cloud of water vapor that seemed to have no substantial form, and it was sending waves upon waves crashing into Luo Qinghai's defenses.

As for Wyrm 3 and Chi Lijiao, they were also being harassed by the same misty figures.

Meanwhile, Han Li was holding his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword tightly while locked in a standoff against his corresponding misty figure.

It seemed that even the misty figure's personality was rather similar to his, and it also adopted a more cautious approach, watching him in a still manner instead of striking right away.

Gongshu Jiu was standing somewhere further away with his arms crossed, and it seemed that he wasn't planning to get involved at all.

All of a sudden, Han Li launched himself forward, and as he did so, he abruptly vanished out of thin air.

In the next instant, he reappeared behind the misty figure before piercing his sword diagonally toward his opponent.

He had just used his Reversal True Axis to drastically enhance his own speed, so the sword strike had come very abruptly.

Right as the tip of his sword was about to pierce into the misty figure's abdomen, it also vanished from the spot, leaving nothing more than a faint wisp of residual mist behind.

Could it be that this thing possesses the same abilities as me?

Han Li's heart jolted slightly as he disappeared from the spot once again.

As soon as he reappeared, he immediately swept his sword horizontally behind him, and sure enough, the misty figure appeared right before him before lashing out with its sword as well.

A sharp clang rang out, and Han Li was forced back several steps by the force of the clash.

The misty figure was also sent sliding back, while the sword in its hand was destroyed by streaks of azure sword qi sweeping toward it.

Gongshu Jiu's brows furrowed ever so slighlty upon seeing this, and he focused his gaze on the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in Han Li's hand.

Chapter 505: Misty Adversaries

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he sized up the misty figure standing before him.

White mist gently swirled around the misty figure's hand, and another longsword slowly took shape.

What on earth is this thing?

Han Li activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes to find that each of the misty figures had a ball of light in their body that was pulsing in a rhythmic fashion.

The misty figure that was battling Daoist Hu Yan had a ball of crimson light in its body, the misty figure facing Luo Qinghai had a blue one, while the ball of light within Han Li's assailant was a light golden color.

However, aside from that, Han Li wasn't able to spot anything else remarkable about these misty figures.

Right as he was wondering whether he should summon his Mantra Treasured Axis to take a closer look, a slightly feeble voice suddenly rang out in his mind, and it belonged to none other than Nan Kemeng.

At this moment, everyone else around Han Li could hear his voice as well.

"These misty figures have no substantial forms, but all of them have law powers in their bodies that correspond with yours. Right above each of their heads is a white thread that's invisible to the naked eye, and these threads are connected to the immortal envoy's fingertips. At the same time, there's also a thread connecting their hearts to yours."

Han Li took a subtle glance at Gongshu Jiu's crossed arms upon hearing this, and sure enough, he could see Gongshu Jiu's fingers making tiny movements that were barely detectable.

It was as if he were a puppeteer that was controlling some puppets on strings.

While battling the misty figure before him, Han Li began to inspect his surroundings to find that all of the other misty figures were wielding the same law powers as the opponents that they had been assigned to.

A look of realization instantly appeared on his face as he called out through voice transmission, "Don't waste any more energy on fighting these misty figures, fellow daoists. All of them are reflections of us that have been conjured up by the immortal envoy's law powers, so their powers are virtually identical to ours, and it won't be an easy task for us to defeat them."

"I've arrived at this realization myself as well, but how are we supposed to defeat these things?" Luo Qinghai asked.

"Do not waste any more of your law powers. These reflections are connected to us through threads of mist, and their law powers are coming straight out of our bodies!" Han Li revealed.

"Now wonder I could feel my law powers being expended so quickly! The rate of expenditure is almost twice the normal rate for me!" Daoist Hu Yan exclaimed.

"He's trying to use these things to wear us down, and once our law powers are completely exhausted, we'll be completely at his mercy," Wyrm 3 said.

"Alright, now that we've identified the crux of the matter, does anyone have a solution?" Chi Lijiao asked.

"These figures possess no intelligence and are being controlled solely by the immortal envoy. Ultimately, this is just an ability of his, so these are nothing more than manifestations of his law powers. All we need to do is stop using our law powers for now and focus all of our attacks on Gongshu Jiu himself. That's the best solution I can think of right now," Han Li proposed.

"Sounds good to me! If things continue like this, we'll be dead soon anyway, so we may as well make a final stand!" Daoist Hu Yan chimed in in agreement.

Luo Qinghai took a glance at Nan Kemeng, and upon receiving a nod from the latter, he immediately declared, "I also agree with this course of action."

Wyrm 3 and Chi Lijiao also expressed their approval of this idea, and with that, all of five of them immediately sprang into action.

The crimson flames over Daoist Hu Yan's body were instantly snuffed out, and he spun around in mid-air, rising up like a tornado before hurtling directly toward the misty figure in front of him.

The flames around the misty figure's body also faded as it rushed at Daoist Hu Yan in the exact same fashion.

The two of them clashed in mid-air with a resounding boom, and Daoist Hu Yan allowed himself to be sent flying by the force of the clash, using it to launch himself at Gonshu Jiu.

Almost at the exact same moment, Han Li and the others also employed various strategies to disengage themselves from their battles against the misty figures before rushing at Gongshu Jiu.

A hint of surprise flashed through Gongshu Jiu's eyes upon seeing this.

"Have you already seen through it? It appears I may have underestimated all of you. Having said that, it's not like it makes any difference," he chuckled, and as soon as his voice trailed off, he abruptly made a wrenching motion with his left hand, upon which all of the misty figures were pulled toward him by a burst of tremendous force, reappearing directly in the paths of Han Li and the others in the blink of an eye.

"You think that it'll somehow make a difference just because you're not using your law powers? You still stand no chance at all!" Gongshu Jiu jeered like a cat toying with some mice.

Right at this moment, a burst of golden ripple suddenly appeared behind him, and Han Li abruptly emerged out of thin air, then lashed out with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

The sword was flashing with golden lightning, and right as it was about to strike Gongshu Jiu's waist, he suddenly vanished amid a flash of white light, replaced by the misty figures in the visage of Han Li.

In just the blink of an eye, he had managed to transpose himself with the misty figure, which was struck by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword and completely torn apart.

Meanwhile, Gongshu Jiu reappeared not far away, and the smile on his face finally faded as a cold and furious look appeared on his face.

A hint of disappointment appeared on Han Li's face in the wake of his failed attack, while Gongshu Jiu's brows furrowed tightly as he mused, "Time law powers... Were you the one who killed Elder Tao's son, Tao Yu? I can't think of anyone else in this immortal region cultivating the Mantra Axis Scripture."

"That's right, I'm the one who killed him," Han Li admitted with a bold grin.

Gongshu Jiu's expression darkened even further as he said, "You can smile all you want now, but I bet you're not going to be able to smile any longer once I take you back to Elder Tao! He's an expert in crafting nascent souls into nascent soul lamps, and you'll be burning for at least 100,000 years at Tao Yu's altar! You'll be in such excruciating pain that you'll wish you had been refined into a Golden Soul Pill instead!"

Han Li's expression remained completely unchanged as he retorted, "I've had a Golden Soul Pill before, but I wonder what a pill refined using a Jade Immortal's nascent soul will taste like."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he took a step forward and launched himself at Gongshu Jiu once again.

"How insolent!"

A cold look appeared on Gongshu Jiu's face, and he continued to control the misty figures that were battling Daoist Hu Yan and the others with his left hand, while simultaneously making a grabbing motion with his right hand to summon a slender longsword that looked as if it had been fashioned out of white jade.

As the sword was slashed through the air, an indistinct burst of qi seemed to flash through the air, then transformed into a series of extremely thin blade projections as it swept toward Han Li.

Han Li immediately activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, which allowed him to identify the trajectories of these blade projections.

At the same time, he slashed his sword through the air repeatedly, unleashing layers upon layers of azure sword qi that formed a protective barrier around him, keeping all of the oncoming blade projections at bay.

At the same time, he couldn't help but feel a little awestruck. It was incredible to him that someone was able to utilize their law powers to this extent. This was truly not a level of mastery that a Golden Immortal could hope to reach.

Due to the fact that he was constantly being suppressed by Gongshu Jiu's spirit domain, it took Han Li a great deal of effort to finally pierce through the layers of blade projections to close down the distance between himself and Gongshu Jiu.

He made a hand seal with one hand while slashing his sword through the air with the other, and all of the layers of azure sword qi around him instantly bloomed like a lotus flower before hurtling toward Gongshu Jiu at once.

Gongshu Jiu's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he raised his sword horizontally in front of him, then slashed it through the air with a flick of his wrist to conjure up a huge wall of white qi.

A string of loud clangs rang out incessantly within the palace, and all of the streaks of azure sword qi pierced into the wall of white qi, but were unable to make it all the way through.

A hint of disappointment appeared in Gongshu Jiu's eyes upon seeing this, and he remarked, "Looks like I overestimated you."

However, right at this moment, a smile suddenly appeared on Han Li's face as he gently flicked his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword with his finger, and all of the streaks of azure sword qi abruptly exploded in unison, releasing an extremely formidable shockwave that blasted a huge hole into the wall of white qi.

The shockwaves continued to proliferate outward, causing the entire palace to tremble violently.

The green pill cauldron originally served as the core of this golden palace, but now that the cauldron had been eaten by Jin Tong and most of the restrictions inscribed onto the ground had been destroyed, a series of cracks began to appear on the walls in the face of these devastating shockwaves.

Gongshu Jiu was situated closest to the explosion, and he couldn't help but stumble back in retreat in the face of these shockwaves.

Before he had a chance to steady himself, a crimson figure abruptly appeared behind him.

He immediately swung around in a manner that seemed to defy the laws of physics, and he discovered that it was Daoist Hu Yan who had arrived on the scene and was slashing his fiery longsword directly at his head.

Gongshu Jiu immediately raised the slender longsword in his hand to parry the attack, and a sharp clang rang out as the pair of swords clashed, sending flames and sword qi erupting in all directions.

In the instant that the two swords clashed, a crimson gourd suddenly flew out of the cloth pouch on Daoist Hu Yan's back, and the opening of the gourd was aimed diagonally downward, directly facing Gongshu Jiu as it hovered above both of their heads.

The ancient runes on the surface of the gourd were flashing incessantly, and it was giving off waves of scorching heat.

Immediately thereafter, the stopper of the gourd flew out on its own with a loud pop.

Chapter 506: Was it Really Worth it

A loud draconic roar instantly rang out across the entire palace, and a mighty black dragon flew out of the opening of the gourd.

The dragon had black flames all over its body, and it opened its mouth before biting down viciously upon Gongshu Jiu.

"Dao Lord Baili!" Luo Qinghai exclaimed upon seeing this.

A hint of enlightenment flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this, and he realized that Daoist Hu Yan had most likely not been trying to secure a High Zenith Pill for himself. Instead, it was to save Baili Yan, who he had been carrying in that gourd of his this entire time.

In the wake of the internal conflict in the Blaze Dragon Dao orchestrated by Xiao Jinhan, Ouyang Kuishan and many of the other dao lords had worked with the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace to surround Baili Yan, and not only did they foil his plan for reaching the High Zenith Stage, a plan that he had been working toward for countless years, they also managed to severely wound him, but he was ultimately able to get away.

Fortunately, Daoist Hu Yan was also able to get away from the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and after leaving the Blaze Dragon Dao, he reunited with Baili Yan, and now, the two of them were here in the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace.

However, what Han Li wanted to know was how Daoist Hu Yan had been aware in advance that there were High Zenith Pills in the immortal manor.

As soon as Baili Yan flew out of the crimson gourd, Daoist Hu Yan had already darted back in retreat.

Scorching black flames erupted out of the black blaze dragon's mouth to instantly inundate Gongshu Jiu, and the misty figures that he was controlling instantly slowed down significantly, as if Gongshu Jiu had temporarily lost control over them.

Everyone immediately pounced on this opportunity to destroy the misty figures, following which they hurriedly gathered around Gongshu Jiu and the blaze dragon.

Close to 20 seconds later, the blaze dragon closed its cavernous mouth, and it shrank down rapidly until it was no larger than the average snake.

"The High Zenith Pill has been beneficial to my recovery and allowed me to expel the karmic fire in my body, but I need more time to refine it, so this is all I can do to help you for now," the blaze dragon said.

"That's fine. Go back into the gourd to rest," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

Baili Yan immediately flew into the gourd upon hearing this, and Daoist Hu Yan stowed the gourd back into the cloth pouch on his back.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and Luo Qinghai and the others were still reeling a little. However, thankfully, Baili Yan's attack had allowed them to get rid of those pesky misty figures while also trapping Gongshu Jiu.

"Everyone, we need to take advantage of this opportunity to refine Gongshu Jiu's physical body, then capture his nascent soul!" Luo Qinghai urged.

Everyone immediately sprang into action upon hearing this, unleashing a barrage of attacks into the black flames around Gongshu Jiu.

Crimson flame, blue light, golden lightning... All manners of attacks surged into the black flames from all directions, compressing it into a fireball that was only around 10 feet in size.

Han Li was scrutinizing the interior of the fireball intently with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and he discovered that there was still a spherical, semi-transparent wall of qi around Gongshu Jiu's body that was keeping all of the flames and attacks at bay.

Furthermore, a layer of faint red light had appeared over the wall of qi, and it was becoming brighter and brighter.

A hint of alarm flashed through everyone's eyes upon seeing this, and they immediately attempted to take evasive measures, but it was already too late.

A burst of incredibly powerful shockwaves erupted in all directions, scattering all of the black flames and everyone's attacks before sending them flying back through the air.

The golden palace was already on the verge of collapse, and it was finally unable to hold itself together any longer, falling in a heap to be reduced to a pile of rubble.

However, before everyone had a chance to stand up from amid the rubble, Gongshu Jiu had already emerged from the wreckage, and he sighed, "I was going to invite all of you to come to our Heavenly Court to repent for your crime so that you can perhaps change your ways, but it seems that my kindness is being treated as weakness."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept his hands through the air, and five bursts of radiant light emerged over his fingertips. Five feathers from some type of unknown bird then flew out from within before hurtling toward Han Li and the others.

The light radiating from the feathers had an illusory quality to it, and it was also giving off bursts of subtle law power fluctuations.

A sense of foreboding welled up in his heart upon seeing this, and he hurriedly raised his sword to defend himself.

With a flick of Wyrm 3's wrist, a silver bracelet that was riddled with ancient patterns slipped off her wrist, then began to revolve in front of her while radiating a vast expanse of bright silver light.

Meanwhile, Chi Lijiao raised both hands in front of himself to summon a golden badge, which transformed into a shimmering golden shield in the blink of an eye.

A string of loud clangs rang out one after another within the palace, and the sword in Han Li's hand was bent to an extreme degree, with its blade crashing heavily into his chest, sending him flying thousands of feet before crashing into a mountain face.

Luo Qinghai had summoned a jade fan treasure to protect himself, but it had been completely pulverized by one of the azure feathers, and a huge hole was punched into his chest while his entire body was slammed into the ground.

Wyrm 3's silver bracelet was shattered, and she was also sent flying through the air, but didn't appear to have sustained any injuries.

As for Chi Lijiao, his golden shield was also destroyed by an azure feather, which then pierced straight through his head, and in the blink of an eye, his nascent soul was captured by Gongshu Jiu.

In order to pick up his crimson gourd, Daoist Hu Yan was already a split second slower to react than everyone else, and by the time he looked up, one of the azure feathers was already no more than three feet away from his chest, so there was no time for him to take evasive measures.

In this dire situation, a figure suddenly shot forth from the side, then positioned themselves in front of him as a meat shield.

"Yun Ni!" both Daoist Hu Yan and Ouyang Kuishan exclaimed in unison.

The former hurriedly grabbed her by the arm in an attempt to drag her away, while the latter's body turned bright red as he unleashed a secret technique to drastically enhance his own speed, arriving in front of Yun Ni an instant before the feather reached her.

A dull thump rang out as the feather pierced through several protective light barriers before punching through Ouyang Kuishan's glabella, pulverizing both his head and his consciousness.

The three crashed heavily into one another and were sent flying together before falling to the ground.

A stunned look appeared on Yun Ni's face as she hurriedly rolled Ouyang Kuishan over, only to find that his eyes had already glazed over, but there was a satisfied smile hanging on his lips.

A complex look appeared on Daoist Hu Yan's face upon seeing this.

Yun Ni took a glance at Daoist Hu Yan, then turned her gaze back to Ouyang Kuishan, and for the first time in countless years, tears began to well up in her eyes.

She had actually met Ouyang Kuishan before Daoist Hu Yan in the Blaze Dragon Dao, and the two of them had embarked on multiple journeys together.

She had always been aware of his feelings, but she had never been able to reciprocate them.

Right at this moment, a golden nascent soul suddenly flew out of Ouyang Kuishan's dantian, and it looked as if it could fade out of existence at any moment, but it was still staring intently at Yun Ni with its tiny eyes.

"Was it really worth it?" Yun Ni asked with tear-filled eyes.

"My entire life, I've pursued greater power in the hope that I'll be able to attain freedom and do whatever I please someday, traveling this immortal region to my heart's content with my beloved dao partner. Unfortunately, the more advanced my cultivation base became, the more I was weighed down by responsibilities. For the first time, I've been able to act completely selfishly and for my own sake, so how was it not worth it?" the nascent soul replied in a feeble voice.

"You've earned my admiration, Ouyang Kuishan! Rest assured, I'll do everything in my power to resurrect you!" Daoist Hu Yan promised as he flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized sandalwood box.

Ouyang Kuishan took a glance at him, then silently flew into the box.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already flown back from the mountain face and descended beside Daoist Hu Yan.

He had naturally witnessed Ouyang Kuishan sacrifice himself for Yun Ni just now, and his expression remained unchanged, but internally, his opinion of Ouyang Kuishan had been improved significantly.

Wyrm 3 took a glance at Chi Lijiao's body, then also flew over to join Han Li and the others. As for Luo Qinghai, he was laying completely still, and it was unclear whether he was dead or unconscious.

Perhaps it was because unleashing those feathers had been too taxing on him, but in any case, Gongshu Jiu didn't unleash any further attacks, instead remaining completely still on the spot.

"Why have you refrained from using your time law powers this entire time? Are you trying to save your energy so you can attempt to make an escape at the right opportunity?" Wyrm 3 asked through voice transmission as she turned to Han Li with a cold expression.

"I have a trump card ability that could perhaps kill Gongshu Jiu in a single strike, but I've expended too much of my time law powers earlier, so I have to be conservative and only strike at the right moment," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"I hope you're not lying. If we manage to get out of here alive, I'll give you the next level of the Spirit Refinement Technique. At your cultivation base, it's next to impossible to escape from a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal, so don't harbor any delusions," Wyrm 3 said.

"I'd advise you to also stop holding back, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3."

As Han Li was speaking, he took a seemingly casual glance at his surroundings to discover that the fair-skinned scholar and the other Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortal had managed to destroy one of the halberd-wielding golden puppets. However, both of them had suffered severe injuries and weren't able to ensure much else aside from self-preservation.

Xue Ying had no intention of sparing them, and she immediately flew in their direction.

Nan Kemeng had also been sent flying by the earlier explosion, and it was unclear where he had fallen.

As for the Golden Immortal from the Blaze Dragon Dao, he was severely outmatched by the remaining halberd-wielding puppet without Ouyang Kuishan's assistance, and it wasn't going to take long before he crashed to a defeat.

"Fellow Daoist Hu Yan, you two should go and help out your fellow dao lord. I'll take care of things here," Han Li suddenly said.

Daoist Hu Yan was rather taken aback to hear this, and Han Li explained, "I'm sure it's already become clear to you that having a numbers advantage doesn't really help us at all against the immortal envoy. If we want to take him down, then we'll have to resort to some unconventional and risky tactics."

"Fine, we'll do as you say. You always seem to have more tricks up your sleeve, and I can never seem to get a good grasp on you. If we get out of here alive, I'll treat you to an entire jar of my finest wine!" Daoist Hu Yan replied with a smile.

"You better not forget that promise!" Han Li chuckled.

Chapter 507: Who Do You Want to Kill?

"What exactly do High Zenith Pills do? Surely it must have some extraordinary effects, considering how desperate Luo Qinghai and the others were to get their hands on these pills," Han Li suddenly asked through voice transmission.

"High Zenith Pills are extremely sought after among all Golden Immortals, but they're just as rare as they are revered," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

"Could it be that it has something to do with making a breakthrough to the High Zenith Stage?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The most important effect of the High Zenith Pill is that it can help cultivators at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage ward off the fifth decay," Daoist Hu Yan confirmed with a nod.

"I see."

Han Li was ecstatic to hear this. Given Daoist Hu Yan's explanation, it was clear that High Zenith Pills to Golden Immortals were no less important than Golden Soul Pills to True Immortals, and they were clearly even more precious.

Furthermore, he had managed to obtain the most premium High Zenith Pill from that entire cauldron, and that was a massive reward to claim.

Daoist Hu Yan stowed away Ouyang Kuishan's body, then flew toward the remaining halberd-wielding puppet with Yun Ni.

Meanwhile, Han Li took a brief moment to inspect his own internal condition, then tightened his grip around his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword as he exchanged a glance with Wyrm 3, indicating for her to prepare to strike.

Right at his moment, a burst of dull rumbling rang out from the golden chair, causing the entire palace to tremble violently.

Even though the palace had already collapsed, the chair remained completely unscathed.

All of a sudden, the living corpse seated on the chair rose to its feet, and its entire body was giving off radiant gray light.

The golden light barrier seemed to have sensed something, and it also began to glow radiantly while countless palm-sized golden runes emerged within it.

However, that still wasn't enough for it to contain the gray light, and before long, thin cracks were beginning to appear on its surface.

A burst of elated laughter rang out from within the golden light barrier, and it wasn't very loud, but everyone who heard it was struck by a burst of sharp pain in the head, as if there were countless red-hot needles piercing into their souls.

Everyone hurriedly channeled their cultivation arts to protect their souls as they darted back in retreat with alarmed looks on their faces.

Han Li also flew back in retreat like everyone else, while Gongshu Jiu cast a bewildered gaze toward the golden chair.

Xue Ying flew over to Gongshu Jiu's side, then also cast her gaze in the same direction.

Inside the light barrier, gray light was churning incessantly, and nine bursts of gray light that resembled plume of smoke surged out of the light barrier before wrapping themselves around the nine golden stone pillars, then snapped them with ease.

The golden light barrier immediately began to tremble violently as the cracks on its surface widened, following which it exploded with a resounding boom.

A figure slowly emerged from the vast expanse of golden light, and it was none other than the middle-aged daoist priest seated on the golden chair.

The daoist priest wore a faint smile as he walked along with his hands clasped behind his back, and he appeared no different from a normal cultivator.

The only remarkable thing about him was that his eyes were entirely gray in color with no whites at all, presenting a rather unsettling sight to behold.

A hint of surprise and befuddlement immediately appeared on Gongshu Jiu's face at the sight of the daoist priest, while Xue Ying asked, "Do you recognize this man, Uncle Gongshu?"

"I certainly wasn't expecting to find a Gray Immortal here. Looks like I really am in luck!" Gongshu Jiu mused as he stared intently at the middle-aged daoist priest like a hawk.

The expressions on the faces of Luo Qinghai and the others all changed drastically upon hearing this, and he immediately swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of blue light that swept up all of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators before flying away into the distance.

The remaining dao lord of the Blaze Dragon Dao also hurriedly flew back to open up some distance between himself and the daoist priest, while Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni exchanged a glance before doing the same.

Han Li didn't know why everyone was so wary of the daoist priest, but he also decided that it was best to maintain his distance, flying over to Daoist Hu Yan's side as he asked through voice transmission, "What is a Gray Immortal, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan?"

The soul fragment had told him some things about Gray Immortals and the Gray Realm, but he hadn't gone into much detail, and it seemed that everyone was quite fearful of this Gray Immortal.

"You may not have heard about this, Fellow Daoist Li, but once upon a time, our Northern Glacial Immortal Realm was actually called the Infernal Frost Immortal Region. The entire immortal region was split into two following a major battle, and that was during the invasion of the Gray Immortals. Gray Immortals are sworn enemies of us immortals, and we don't know exactly where they come from, but it's said that they can devour immortals.

“During that battle, all of the sects and powers in the entirety of the Infernal Frost Immortal Region joined forces while also recruiting some reinforcements from other immortal regions, and it was only with their combined powers that they were able to force the Gray Immortals into retreat.

“However, close to half of all of the immortal region's sects were wiped out, and many races were eradicated altogether. Ever since then, no other Gray Immortals have appeared in this immortal region," Daoist Hu Yan informed.

"Why is it that I've never heard of any of this before?" Han Li asked with a stunned expression.

"The battle that I mentioned took place a very long time ago, and the Heavenly Court has always intentionally tried to conceal those past events, so only some of the top sects in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, such as the Blaze Dragon Dao and the Vast Flow Palace, are aware of these events.

“You're still quite young, and you were only in the Blaze Dragon Dao for a very short time, so it's no surprise that you haven't heard about any of this," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

What Daoist Hu Yan had just said matched what the soul fragment had described, and with that, Han Li was able to confirm that the soul fragment had been telling the truth, at least in this regard.

Right at this moment, a streak of red light descended beside the middle-aged daoist priest, then faded to reveal Wyrm 3, who extended a slight bow toward him.

"Welcome back to the Immortal Realm, Daoist Master Mo Yu!"

Luo Qinghai and the others were all quite alarmed to see this, clearly not expecting Wyrm 3 to be familiar with this Gray Immortal.

Meanwhile, Han Li was also looking at the middle-aged daoist priest with a hint of surprise in his eyes.

He had already heard from the soul fragment that the Reincarnation Palace had worked with Gray Immortals in the past, so he wasn't that surprised to see that Wyrm 3 had ties with this Gray Immortal, but this didn't match the story that the soul fragment had told him.

According to the soul fragment, Mo Yu was the name of the High Zenith Stage Gray Immortal that had triggered the Gray Immortal invasion of the Northern Glacial Immortal Realm, but it had also told him that Mo Yu was a female disciple under the Infernal Frost Immortal Lord, while this Gray Immortal was clearly a man, so what exactly was the truth?

Before Han Li had a chance to ponder this matter any further, Gongshu Jiu suddenly exclaimed, "So you're Mo Yu! I had heard that you had gone missing in the wake of that battle all those years ago, is this where you've been hiding this entire time?"

The middle-aged daoist priest paid no heed to Gongshu Jiu as he turned to Wyrm three and said, "Oh? I'm surprised there's still someone who remembers me. Who are you?"

"I am Wyrm 3 of the Reincarnation Palace," Wyrm 3 replied.

Red light flashed over her body as she spoke, and in the blink of an eye, she transformed into a beautiful woman in a red dress, but her face was concealed behind a crimson dragon mask.

"Wym 3, is it? I suppose I owe you a favor now. Who do you want to kill?" Mo Yu asked as he swept his gaze over his surroundings.

Wyrm 3 offered no reply to this, merely pointing a finger in Gongshu Jiu's direction before flying away to the side.

Mo Yu turned his gaze to Gongshu Jiu with a faint smile, but he then suddenly turned his attention to Han Li.

"You're in a real sorry state, kid. You're bringing shame upon the laws of time! I'll chat with you after I've returned this favor," Mo Yu chuckled, and everyone else present immediately turned to Han Li with peculiar looks in their eyes upon hearing this.

"How are you related to this Gray Immortal, Fellow Daoist Li?" Daoist Hu Yan asked through voice transmission.

"That's a bit of a long story. I encountered that soul fragment of his in an underground palace, and I brought it with me after I left. At this point, I still don't know whether he's friend or foe," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"Could it be that you really did enter the legendary Moonlight Palace?" Daoist Hu Yan exclaimed with wide eyes.

"It looks like that must've been it," Han Li replied.

Meanwhile, Mo Yu's gaze returned to Gongshu Jiu, and he sighed in a resigned manner, "I'm not someone who likes to owe favors to other people, so I'm afraid you're going to have to die here. How would you like to die?"

"How laughable! Your soul has only just been restored, and your cultivation base is still unsteady! You're just bluffing to try and buy time for yourself!" Gongshu Jiu harrumphed coldly as he made a hand seal, and 10 misty white figures emerged in front of him, each of which was several times larger than the ones from before, and all of them pounced at Mo Yu at once.

"Oh crap, you got me! I didn't think you'd see through me so quickly! Are all immortal envoys this smart nowadays?" Mo Yu exclaimed as feigned a panicked expression, only to then blast a streak of gray light out of the palm of his hand as he declared, "One attack is all I'll need to kill you!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, the streak of gray light exploded into countless gray threads, all of which were flying through the air at an incredible speed before piercing through the bodies of the misty white figures in the blink of an eye.

All 10 of the misty figures were instantly rooted to the spot, then exploded into a vast expanse of white mist, much to the surprise and incredulity of Han Li and the others.

Those misty figures had caused them no shortage of trouble earlier, yet this Gray Immortal had just eradicated 10 of them in the blink of an eye!

After piercing through the misty figures, the gray threads continued to hurtle directly toward Gongshu Jiu, who remained completely unfazed as he opened his mouth to release a ball of white light, which transformed into an antiquated white mirror.

The antiquated mirror released a burst of white light that was filled with countless runes, and it formed a thick white cocoon of light around his entire body.

Mo Yu immediately switched to a different hand seal upon seeing this, and all of the threads of gray light converged toward a single spot, forming a thick gray arrow in the blink of an eye.

A formidable glacial aura was emanating from the arrow, and it was different from any type of law power, but was also not inferior to any of them.

A series of gray corkscrews of light also appeared around the arrow, and they began to revolve rapidly while giving off a terrifying screeching sound.

Chapter 508: Perfect Opportunity

As soon as the cocoon of white light took shape, the arrow of gray light also arrived, and the latter struck the former with tremendous force.

The white cocoon was instantly shattered like an eggshell to reveal Gongshu Jiu inside, and the gray arrow had already pierced through his body.

A large hole had been punched through his chest, and blood instantly began to flow out of all of his orifices.

Just as Mo Yu declared, it had only taken him a single attack to strike down Gongshu Jiu!

Han Li was very much taken aback to see this, but also quite relieved.

However, in the next instant, Gongshu Jiu's body abruptly dissipated into a cloud of white mist, following which he reappeared behind Mo Yu, then immediately opened his mouth to release a burst of dazzling five-colored light, within which was a semi-transparent crystalline rock.

The rock was surrounded by arcs of dazzling five-colored light, and it was giving off an incredibly destructive aura.

Mo Yu's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly fled to the side while a burst of gray flames appeared around him to form a fiery gray barrier.

However, it was already too late, and the five-colored rock caught up to him in the blink of an eye, then exploded into a ball of blinding five-colored lightning that inundated his entire body in an instant.

The destructive power erupting out of the burst of five-colored lightning was over 10 times more formidable than that of the pill tribulations from before, and the space around the five-colored lightning immediately became severely warped and fractured, looking as if it could shatter at any moment.

Arcs of five-colored lightning sprang forth in all directions, causing the surrounding space to tremble violently, and everyone hurriedly took evasive measures, flying back in retreat as quickly as they could.

Within the blinding five-colored light, Mo Yu had vanished without a trace, and it seemed that his body had been completely eradicated.

A faint smile appeared on Gongshu Jiu's face upon seeing this, while Han Li and the others looked on with grim expressions.

If Mo Yu really had been slain, then they would once again be in a dire situation.

The five-colored lightning flashed a few times before quickly fading away.

All of a sudden, Gongshu Jiu's expression stiffened as a ball of gray light emerged where the five-colored lightning had been just a moment ago. The ball of light was around the same height as a grown man, and there were wisps of dense gray qi swirling around it.

The gray light then parted to reveal Mo Yu once again, and his complexion was a little pale, but aside from that, he was completely unscathed, and even his clothes were completely undamaged.

"You're a Gray Immortal, how could you possibly have survived Heavenly Damnation Lightning? This is impossible!" Gongshu Jiu exclaimed in incredulity.

"I didn't think that you would have a Heavenly Damnation Lightning Stone, but unfortunately for you, it's one of the lowest caliber, and that won't be enough to kill me," Mo Yu said with a shake of his head.

Gongshu Jiu immediately turned and fled toward the entrance of the palace as a streak of white light.

"Hey, don't run! I have to keep my promises!" Mo Yu yelled as he swept his right hand through the air, and his left arm instantly exploded into a ball of dense gray light, which transformed into a gray chain that shot forth through the air in a flash.

In the next instant, the gray chain appeared around Gongshu Jiu, then wrapped itself around him in a flash.

Bright gray light erupted out of Mo Yu's body before spreading outward, instantly forming a gray spirit domain with countless gray shadows swirling within it.

He then began to chant an incantation, and all of the gray shadows within the spirit domain converged toward a single spot to form an enormous gray dragon's head.

The draconic head was riddled with black runes, and it was giving off a terrifying glacial aura that was only becoming more and more formidable by the second.

In the instant the draconic head took shape, Han Li and the others were all instantly struck by a burst of sharp pain all over the entirety of their bodies, and they felt as if even their bone marrow were being frozen solid.

The protective spiritual light around them was completely ineffective in warding off this glacial aura, and they hurriedly flew away even further to protect themselves.

Gongshu Jiu's expression finally darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he let loose a low roar as balls of dazzling white flames abruptly erupted out of his body.

Every single one of these white fireballs were giving off tremendous law power fluctuations, and they were scorching the gray chain intently while he was also struggling to free himself with all his might.

The gray chain immediately began to creak and groan, and it looked as if it could burst apart at any moment, but at this point, the gray draconic head had already completely taken shape, and it took up virtually the entire palace.

Its skin was riddled with gray scales that were giving off a cold gleam, and two balls of gray fire lit up within its huge eye sockets as it cast its gaze toward Gongshu Jiu.

A thunderous roar rang out as it opened its cavernous mouth to release a pillar of black light that struck Gongshu Jiu with tremendous force, resulting in an incredibly bright eruption of gray light that forced everyone to shield their eyes and look away.

After the gray light faded, Han Li discovered that Gongshu Jiu had been sent flying into one of the collapsed walls of the palace.

His body was virtually completely embedded into the wall, and his robes had been torn to shreds. His hair was completely disheveled, and it was clear that he had suffered extremely severe injuries.

"That's all you've got? How frail. I don't even feel like playing around with you anymore," Mo Yu sighed as he made a hand seal, and another burst of blinding gray light emerged within the mouth of the gray draconic head.

An alarmed look appeared on Gongshu Jiu's face as he hurriedly flew out of the wall as a streak of white light, and he didn't even have time to address his own injuries as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a small white flag and a yellow badge, which began to rapidly revolve around him to form a protective barrier.

Right at this moment, a pained look suddenly appeared on Mo Yu's face, and he began to tremble uncontrollably, while his gray spirit domain also began to ripple violently.

A dull thump rang out as the gray draconic head exploded into a vast expanse of gray light, following which the entire spirit domain also vanished in a flash.

Gongshu Jiu was quite taken aback by this turn of events, but an ecstatic look then appeared on his face as he fled into the distance.

Right at this moment, a streak of golden light flashed past, and a figure appeared in Gongshu Jiu's path in the blink of an eye.

It was none other than Han Li, and radiant golden light erupted out of his body as he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which immediately began to revolve rapidly.

Countless golden ripples surged out of the axis before encompassing Gongshu Jiu's entire body, instantly stopping him cold in his tracks.

Han Li then raised a hand to send an azure flying sword hurtling out of his sleeve, and it instantly swelled to over 100 feet in length, while thick arcs of golden lightning that were imbued with an incredibly destructive aura erupted over its surface.

A cold gleam flashed through his eyes as he made a hand seal, and the giant azure sword abruptly appeared in front of Gongshu Jiu in a flash before crashing down with immense power.

Gongshu Jiu was already aware of the fact that he was a member of the Reincarnation Palace, so if he were to get away, then there would be no end to Han Li's troubles.

He had already determined that even High Zenith Stage Jade Immortals weren't impervious to his time law powers. Prior to this, he had no chance of getting close to Gongshu Jiu, but the perfect opportunity had just presented itself.

During the earlier battle, Xue Ying had made sure to keep her distance, but she immediately swooped onto the scene upon seeing this.

Things had progressed completely differently from what she had anticipated, but she was naturally not going to allow a mere mid-Golden Immortal cultivator to do as he pleased.

As she flew through the air, she released a burst of white light out of her sleeve, and it contained a white rope immortal treasure that hurtled toward the giant azure sword.

However, as soon as the white rope entered the golden ripples, it was immediately slowed down to the point that it looked as if it had fallen completely still.

Xue Ying had never seen Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis before, so she was very much taken aback by this turn of events.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face as he abruptly expanded the golden ripples outward, and they instantly swelled in diameter by twofold to encompass Xue Ying as well.

As soon as she was caught within the golden ripples, Xue Ying was also rooted to the spot, and the shocked look on her face had also completely stiffened.

After trapping Xue Ying, Han Li pointed a finger at his giant azure sword, and it began to glow radiantly as it crashed down upon Gongshu Jiu.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the giant azure sword was sent flying back, and it was trembling violently, while the spiritual light around it was flickering erratically.

A surprised look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he hurriedly made a hand seal to stabilize his sword.

He then turned to Gongshu Jiu to discover that an eggshell-like ball of white light had appeared around him.

The ball of light was riddled with runes that were quite strange in appearance, and they weren't golden seal text, nor beveled silver text.

The runes were arranged in a way that resembled the patterns on the back of a turtle's shell, and it was somehow able to withstand an all-out strike from Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he made a hand seal, and the giant azure sword immediately lit up once again as it hurtled toward Gongshu Jiu.

At the same time, two more identical Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords emerged around him, and these two swords also swelled drastically in size before crashing down upon Gongshu Jiu with tremendous power.

Three earth-shattering booms rang out in unison, but all their swords were sent flying back once again, while the ball of light only rippled slightly before falling still again.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

Chapter 509: Ferocious Assault

At this point, Mo Yu's complexion had already improved slightly, and the gray light around him was no longer flickering, but instead of re-entering the fray, he was observing Han Li and Gongshu Jiu from the sidelines with an intrigued look on his face.

"That's a Myriad Law Bead! I didn't think that a mere immortal envoy would have so many fine treasures in his possession. It would almost be a pity to destroy this bead."

Wyrm 3 was also watching Han Li and Gongshu Jiu, and it was unclear what she was thinking.

As for Luo Qinghai and the others, they were all displaying different reactions to Han Li's abrupt interception.

Han Li took a glance at Mo Yu and Wyrm 3, and his brows furrowed slightly as he made a hand seal in preparation to lash out with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords again.

Right at this moment, a burst of white light suddenly flashed over Gongshu Jiu's body, and a burst of tremendous law power fluctuations erupted out of the ball of white light to strike the golden ripples, which immediately began to flicker erratically, while the time law powers within them were thrown into a state of disarray.

A surprised look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

With so many Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis, it was actually already far more powerful than his time spirit domain, albeit with a much more limited range, and this was the first time that someone had been able to disrupt it to this extent.

As expected, a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal was not to be underestimated.

Despite this, Han Li remained completely unfazed as he made a rapid string of hand seals, and his Mantra Treasured Axis began to revolve even faster while the Time Dao Runes on its surface released a burst of radiant golden light, injecting bursts of time law powers into the surrounding golden ripples to stabilize them.

However, before the disruption could be completely quelled, another burst of tremendous law power fluctuations erupted out of the ball of white light to strike the golden ripples, and this time, they began to flicker and tremble even more erratically than before.

Han Li was doing everything in his power to stabilize the golden ripples, but the law power fluctuations surging out of the ball of white light were relentless, and each wave was more powerful than the previous one.

Before long, the golden ripples were beginning to fall part.

Mo Yu's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he remarked, "Looks like even with mastery over one of the three paramount laws, it's too much to ask for a Golden Immortal to take down a Jade Immortal."

He then proceeded to step forward, but Wyrm 3 stopped him as she interjected, "Don't force yourself, Mo Yu. Allow me."

"Well, I'm certainly more than happy to sit back and watch," Mo Yu replied in a lackadaisical voice.

Right at this moment, Luo Qinghai suddenly swept a sleeve through the air to summon a tall blue stone plaque that was riddled with blue patterns and giving off a peculiar aura.

He then pressed both hands against the stone plaque, and everyone around him immediately followed suit.

Even Nan Kemeng had flown over to his side, and his face was as pale as a sheet, but he pressed his palms against the stone plaque as well.

A burst of translucent blue light with countless runes flashing within it erupted out of the stone plaque, then instantly enveloped all of them before flying away at an incredible speed, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

The Blaze Dragon Dao dao lord's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately opened his mouth to release several balls of crimson light, which encompassed his entire body before also carrying him away into the distance in a flash.

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni were also struck by the urge to retreat upon seeing this, but they were hesitant to leave Han Li behind.

"Get out of here, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan. I did that Gray Immortal a favor by bringing him out of that underground palace, so he has no reason to target me. There's no telling what could happen from here, and the longer you stay, the more danger you'll be in," Han Li urged through voice transmission.

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni exchanged a hesitant glance with one another upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, Mo Yu suddenly began to approach the two of them as he complained, "Why are all of you so scared of me? I'm a good person!"

His words of reassurance achieved the completely opposite effect, and Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni immediately flew away in the distance at the sight of the approaching Mo Yu.

"How sad. I'm the savior here, yet I'm being treated like a villain," Mo Yu sighed with a shake of his head, and he made no attempt to pursue Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni as he turned his gaze back to Han Li.

Right at this moment, Wyrm 3 abruptly appeared on the edge of the golden ripples, then raised both hands to release two streaks of yellow light, within which were a pair of long yellow needles.

The pair of needles were giving off formidable earth law power fluctuations as they shot forth toward Gongshu Jiu, but they were also immediately stopped cold in their tracks upon flying into the golden ripples.

"What are you doing, Fellow Daoist Li?" Wyrm 3 asked as she turned to Han Li with furrowed brows.

Han Li could only give a wry smile in response.

Prior to mastering the laws of time, the golden ripples released by his Mantra Treasured Axis hadn't been all that formidable, and he had been able to control them back then so that they didn't slow down his allies and their attacks.

However, now that he had reached the Golden Immortal Stage and made significant strides in his mastery over the laws of time, his Mantra Treasured Axis had become countless times more powerful, but it had also become unwieldy and uncontrollable.

Wyrm 3 seemed to have realized what the problem was upon seeing Han Li's expression, and her brows furrowed even tighter.

If Han Li couldn't control these golden ripples, then there was no way for her to help him.

Han Li took a deep breath as he summoned his time spirit domain to help him stabilize the golden ripples, but his efforts were proving to be largely futile.

The golden ripples were becoming thinner and thinner, and at this rate, they weren't going to last much longer.

The restrictive effect that the Mantra Treasured Axis had on Xue Ying was also significantly diminished, and a burst of law power fluctuations erupted out of her body as well to fight back against the golden ripples.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he quickly made a hand seal, upon which the area encompassed within the golden ripples instantly shrank down to a radius of no more than 1,000 feet, thereby releasing Xue Ying.

Xue Ying was ecstatic to have been freed, but she then took a fearful glance at Han Li and Wyrm 3 before immediately fleeing the scene, making no further attempt to assist Gongshu Jiu.

A cold look appeared on Wyrm 3's face upon seeing this, and she immediately pointed a finger in Xue Ying's direction.

At this point, her pair of yellow needles had also been freed, and they immediately shot forth toward Xue Ying at an incredible speed.

As for Xue Ying, her speed was hampered by Han Li's time spirit domain, so the yellow needles were able to catch up to her in an instant.

Immediately thereafter, countless yellow runes surged out of the pair of needles, forming a pair of large yellow nets that surrounded Xue Ying from all directions.

Both nets were giving off tremendous law power fluctuations, and they quickly ensnared Xue Ying before shrinking down to form a yellow ball in the blink of an eye.

A pleased look appeared in Wyrm 3's eyes upon seeing this, following which she turned her gaze back to Han Li with a contemplative expression.

In terms of overall power, Xue Ying was only slightly inferior to her, so it shouldn't have been anywhere near this easy for Wyrm 3 to capture her, yet here in this time spirit domain, Xue Ying had been caught in an instant.

However, right at this moment, the yellow ball began to bulge violently, swelling to several times its original size, and many small holes began to appear on its surface.

Beams of radiant white light were bursting through these holes, and they erupted forth in all directions before converging to a single spot to reform Xue Ying's body.

However, in the wake of that brief ordeal, her face was looking a little pale, and as soon as she broke free from the yellow ball, she immediately continued to flee the scene even faster than before, reaching the edge of Han Li's time spirit domain in the blink of an eye.

Wyrm 3's expression darkened slightly as she gave a cold harrumph, and a burst of dark red light instantly erupted out of her body before expanding outward rapidly to form a dark red spirit domain in the blink of an eye, encompassing the fleeing Xue Ying within.

Countless bursts of dark red light were surging throughout the spirit domain, significantly slowing down the streak of white light around Xue Ying while also constantly whittling away at it.

Right at this moment, the Wyrm 3's dark red spirit domain and Han Li's golden spirit domain suddenly overlapped with one another, and both spirit domains abruptly lit up significantly, as if they were resonating with one another.

The two spirit domains then began to buzz and tremble, and a series of golden flowers appeared in the sky before drifting down from above.

Not only had Han Li's spirit domain brightened significantly, the same had happened to his golden ripples as well, and they were instantly stabilized, trapping Gongshu Jiu firmly within once again.

With both the time spirit domain and the dark red spirit domain becoming several times brighter, Xue Ying was also stopped cold in her tracks, unable to move any further.

Both Han Li and Wyrm 3 exchanged a bewildered glance upon seeing this, while a hint of surprise appeared in Mo Yu's eyes as well.

Han Li and Wyrm 3 had no idea what was happening here, but both of them knew that this wasn't the time to ponder such matters, so they immediately returned their attention to the battle at hand.

Wyrm 3 made a hand seal, and the yellow ball exploded, transforming into a pair of long, yellow needles once again.

Radiant yellow light erupted out of the pair of needles, and they vanished without a trace, then appeared beside Xue Ying an instant later before sweeping directly through her.

Her body was instantly severed into several pieces, and blood was sent splattering in all directions.

Han Li paid no heed to what was happening on that end as he continued to stare intently at Gongshu Jiu.

Trapped inside Wyrm 3's dark red spirit domain, the ball of white light around Gongshu Jiu had dimmed significantly, and this was naturally quite an encouraging sight for Han Li as a burst of radiant purplish-golden light erupted out of his body.

At the same time, several balls of light of different colors flew out of his body as well, then transformed into a series of different true spirit projections.

These projections revolved around Han Li momentarily before fusing back into his body, and he immediately began to swell drastically in stature.

A layer of purplish-golden scales appeared over his body, and in the blink of an eye, he had transformed into a purplish-golden giant that was over 1,000 feet tall.

The muscles on his shoulders and beneath his ribs squirmed in a rather grotesque fashion, following which two heads and four arms sprang out of his body.

Han Li knew that it was time to pull out all the stops, and he had unleashed his Holy Nirvana Physique!

Chapter 510: Slaying a Jade Immortal

The purplish-golden giant's entire body was riddled with countless golden and silver spirit patterns, and 36 specks of starlight had appeared on its lower abdomen. The combination of the radiant starlight and the dazzling purplish-golden light emanating from the giant's body made this form appear far more formidable than in the past.

Blue light flashed within Han Li's eyes as he let loose a low roar, and an incredibly formidable aura erupted out of his body, causing the surrounding space to tremble violently and sending rings of visible ripples surging outward in all directions.

A peculiar look flashed through Wyrm 3's eyes at the sight of Han Li's Holy Nirvana Physique, and Mo Yu was also quite taken aback by the sight of this transformation.

Han Li made a grabbing motion with all six of his hands, and the three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew into his grasp.

He then opened his mouth to release three translucent golden threads, which vanished into the three giant swords in a flash.

The azure light radiating from the three swords instantly brightened by severalfold, as did the arcs of golden lightning flashing over them, and they transformed into countless golden lightning runes that swirled around the three swords.

The surrounding space shuddered once again in the face of the three swords' collective aura, while Han Li's Heavy Water True Axis appeared in one of three vacant hands.

As for the final two hands, a pair of purplish-golden weapons, namely a giant ax and a massive hammer, had taken shape within them.

These two weapons had been formed purely by spiritual power, but they were also giving off incredibly formidable auras.

Han Li took a step forward, and he abruptly vanished from the spot, then reappeared in front of the ball of white light an instant later before swinging all six of his weapons down upon it.

The three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, the Heavy Water True Axis, and the two purplish-golden weapons struck the ball of white light with an earth-shattering boom, causing it to tremble violently, while the part that had been struck caved in significantly.

However, the ball of light was incredibly resilient, and not only was it able to hold itself intact, it was able to repel all of Han Li's weapons.

However, after withstanding those attacks, the ball of white light had dimmed slightly.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he immediately continued his assault, swinging his weapons down in a relentless barrage.

The sound of Han Li's weapons pounding down onto the ball of white light resembled that of countless thunderclaps ringing out at once, releasing a burst of terrifying power that caused the nearby space to warp violently.

Mo Yu and Wyrm 3 were both astonished to see this.

Before long, the ball of white light was completely inundated by the barrage of furious attacks,and it resembled a tiny raft that was swaying unsteadily on a turbulent sea.

The light that was emanating from it was becoming dimmer and dimmer, and before long, only a thin layer of it remained.

Right at this moment, Han Li let loose a thunderous roar as blinding purplish-golden light erupted out of his body. His six arms became significantly thicker and stronger, while the six weapons in his hands also lit up significantly as they crashed down upon the ball of white light one final time.

A loud crack rang out as the ball of light was finally shattered into countless specks of white light, and Gongshu Jiu was revealed underneath with his hair completely disheveled.

Blood was also pouring out of all of his orifices, seemingly from the impact of all of Han Li's prior attacks, and there was an astonished look on his face.

A white bead was hanging in front of his chest, and it quickly shattered, just like the ball of white light.

Han Li's six weapons were stopped in their tracks for a brief moment before continuing to crash down upon Gongshu Jiu, and a dull thump rang out as he was smashed into a pile of mincemeat.

A relieved look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, but right at this moment, a nascent soul that was as fair and translucent as jade flew out Gongshu Jiu's remains.

Around the nascent soul were several dozen wisps of white flames, which formed the shape of a lotus flower that encompassed the nascent soul within it.

Each wisp of these white flames had a translucent law thread within it, but these law threads were slowly shrinking, as if they were burning away.

A burst of incredibly formidable law powers erupted out of the white flames to force the golden ripples away, following which the white nascent soul vanished into thin air.

An alarmed look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, but he didn't panic, and his Law Destruction Eye instantly appeared on his glabella.

The eye was flashing with a cold black gleam as it scoured the surrounding area.

At the same time, a translucent spiritual sense chain shot out of his glabella as well, then also vanished into thin air in a flash.

This spiritual sense chain was completely different from before. Not only had it become over two times thicker than in the past, a series of silver runes were also swirling around it, giving off a burst of law power fluctuations.

Immediately thereafter, a dull thump rang out, and the translucent chain emerged over 10,000 feet away, with the white nascent soul ensnared within it.

The nascent soul was flailing its little arms with all its might, fanning the white flames around it to incinerate the translucent chain, but the latter remained as resilient as an immovable mountain.

"You're not getting away!" Han Li declared with a cold sneer on his face as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword that instantly transformed into a thin azure and golden thread.

A peerlessly sharp aura was surging out of the thin thread, causing the nearby space to tremble and sway.

The thin thread appeared in front of the white nascent soul in the blink of an eye, then pierced straight into its glabella, passing through with some difficulty.

With a hole punched into the nascent soul's glabella, the white flames around it instantly subsided, and Gongshu Jiu's consciousness completely faded, leaving only a pure nascent soul crystal behind.

Only then did Han Li heave a sigh of relief as he quickly reverted back to his human form.

His complexion had paled significantly, and he quickly withdrew his time spirit domain and his Mantra Treasured Axis as well.

The combination of his spirit domain, Mantra Treasured Axis, and Holy Nirvana Physique had been extremely taxing to unleash all at once, and at this point, his immortal spiritual power had already been completely exhausted.

He raised a hand to make a beckoning motion, and the golden and azure sword thread flew back into his body with something wrapped within it, while the other two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and the Heavy Water True Axis were also stowed away.

He then flipped a hand over to produce a pair of pills that he promptly devoured, and only then did his complexion improve slightly.

With Han Li's time spirit domain withdrawn, Wyrm 3's dark red spirit domain instantly returned to normal, and she took a long glance at Han Li before withdrawing her spirit domain as well.

After taking a moment to recover, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure that swept up Gongshu Jiu's storage bracelet, a pair of immortal treasures, and that white nascent soul.

"Well done, kid! To think that a mere Golden Immortal like yourself was able to slay a High Zenith cultivator! If word of this were to escape, then the entire Immortal Realm would be in awe! The paramount laws are truly not to be underestimated," Mo Yu praised with a smile as he flew over to Han Li's side.

However, Han Li knew that he couldn't take full credit for killing Gongshu Jiu. If it weren't for the fact that his spirit domain had resonated with Wyrm 3's, thereby significantly enhancing its power, there was no way it would've been able to contain Gongshu Jiu.

With that in mind, the thought of the two Dawn Fall Sect Golden Immortals sprang into his mind. Their yin and yang law powers had enhanced one another in much the same way as the spirit domain resonance that had just taken place.

Han Li cast his gaze toward Mo Yu as he asked, "Who exactly are you? Should I be calling you the Boundless Daoist right now, or Gray Immortal Mo Yu?"

"I am Gray Immortal Mo Yu, not the Boundless Daoist," Mo Yu replied with a smile.

Han Li didn't seem all that surprised to hear this, and he asked, "In that case, how much of what you told me about the Boundless Daoist and the Infernal Frost Immortal Lord is actually true?"

"I concealed my identity so that you would be willing to take me with you out of the Moonlight Palace, but everything else I told you is all true. The Boundless Daoist and the Infernal Frost Immortal Lord are one and the same. In fact, she's here right now," Mo Yu said as he cast his gaze toward a certain direction.

Han Li and Wyrm 3 were both rather taken aback to hear this, and they turned to the same direction.

"Why are you not showing yourself?" Mo Yu asked in a gentle voice.

A burst of spatial fluctuations emerged in that direction, and to Han Li's surprise, Lu Yuqing appeared before his eyes.

However, her disposition had undergone a complete change, and she was giving a peerlessly cold and sharp aura, as if she were the personification of a mighty sword.

"We finally meet again after so many years apart," Mo Yu said as he looked deep into Lu Yuqing's eyes, then approached her before grabbing onto her hands.

Lu Yuqing's cold facade instantly crumbled, and a faint blush appeared on her face as she complained, "What are you doing? There are people watching..."

"That decision of mine kept us apart for so many years, and it almost permanently separated us. Now that we've been reunited, I'm never going to let go of you again," Mo Yu said in a firm voice.

Lu Yuqing briefly put up a halfhearted struggle, then gave up and allowed Mo Yu to do as he pleased.

Han Li and Wyrm 3 were feeling a little awkward, and both of them looked away.

At the same time, the image of Nangong Wan sprang into Han Li's mind, and he couldn't help but heave a forlorn internal sigh.

Chapter 511: Unexpected

All of a sudden, a pained yelp snapped Han Li out of his train of thought.

Han Li turned in that direction to find Mo Yu with his head cocked to the side, and there was a pained look on his face, while his ear was plucked upward by Lu Yuqing.

Wyrm 3 was also rather flabbergasted to see this.

"I told you to stop! You think you can just ignore what I say now?" Lu Yuqing yelled in an angry voice, presenting a stark contrast to the shy display that she had put on just a moment ago.

"Ow! Ow! You're going to tear it off! I'm sorry! I apologize! Please..." Mo Yu hurriedly implored in an agonized voice.

"You always apologize, but when have you ever actually changed? If it wasn't for you, neither of us would've ended up like this!"

Lu Yuqing raised her hand further as she spoke, and Mo Yu's head was also plucked up a bit further as a result.

"I already apologized, didn't I? Please forgive me, there are people watching..." Mo Yu implored as he put on a fawning smile.

Lu Yuqing took a glance at Han Li and Wyrm 3, then gave a cold harrumph as she let go of Mo Yu's ear.

Mo Yu hurriedly clasped a hand over his ear while giving Lu Yuqing a sycophantic smile, looking much like a puppy eagerly trying to suck up to its owner.

"Why did you let those people from the Vast Flow Palace get away? If the Heavenly Court learns of what happened here, you know what the outcome is going to be," Lu Yuqing asked with furrowed brows.

"Those are just small fry, it doesn't matter whether they get away or not. Besides, even if I had killed them, there's still no way that the news of our resurrection could be kept secret," Mo Yu replied.

Lu Yuqing raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and before she could respond, Mo Yu abruptly turned and cast his gaze toward Han Li and Wyrm 3 as he declared, "It's all thanks to you two that we were able to finally reunite with each other. I'm no saint or gentleman, but I've always paid sure to repay those who have been kind to me, so if you have any requests, feel free to state them, and we'll do our best to fulfill those requests."

Lu Yuqing continued to glower at Mo Yu for a moment, then also turned to Han Li as she said, "Thank you for protecting me all this time, Fellow Daoist Han. It was only thanks to your help that I was able to recover my memories. If I don't repay this favor, then my dao heart will be inhibited, so please do tell us how we can make it up to you."

"Fellow Daoist Han? Weren't those people calling you Fellow Daoist Li earlier? What is your actual name?" Mo Yu asked.

"A name is nothing more than a title. You can just call me Li Feiyu," Han Li replied.

"Even after all we've been through together, you're still hiding your name? Aren't you being a little too cautious?" Mo Yu grumbled in a disgruntled voice.

Wyrm 3 was clearly also curious to hear Han Li's real name, but she didn't say anything.

Han Li didn't want to dwell on this topic any longer, so he turned to Lu Yuqing as he said, "In that case, I'm happy to oblige. Even though I've attained a spirit domain, I'm still not able to completely control it. Both of you are far more experienced with spirit domains than I am, so I'd like you to teach me how to use my spirit domain."

Mo Yu and Lu Yuqing exchanged a glance with one another upon hearing this, following which the former said, "Due to the disparities in the law powers mastered by each person, the way that a spirit domain is used will also differ from person to person, and the only way to truly master one's spirit domain is through experimentation.

“Having said that, experiences and insights from others may prove to be useful. These are the insights that I've gleaned from all my years experimenting with my spirit domain, you can have them for reference purposes."

Mo Yu flicked a finger through the air as he spoke, sending a gray jade slip flying toward Han Li.

Han Li caught the jade slip, then briefly inspected its contents with his spiritual sense, following which a faint smile appeared on his face. "You have my thanks."

"What would you like, Wyrm 3?" Mo Yu asked as he turned to Wyrm 3.

A contemplative look appeared in Wyrm 3's eyes, and she didn't immediately respond . Only after a brief silence did she reply, "I came here to save you on someone else's orders, so there's no need to compensate me. Having said that, during my time in the Reincarnation Palace, I've always heard that you're an extremely knowledgeable and experienced person, so I would like to ask you a question."

"Go ahead," Mo Yu prompted with a slight nod.

"Just now, my spirit domain resonated with Fellow Daoist Li's, and as a result, both of our spirit domains were significantly enhanced. Do you know why that happened?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"Throughout the entire Immortal Realm, the vast majority of Golden Immortals have mastered at least one type of law powers. For those who haven't mastered any law powers, withstanding the three decays is far too difficult, and progressing to the Golden Immortal Stage is next to impossible for them. Generally speaking, the more advanced one's mastery over their law powers, the more powerful their spirit domain will be.

“However, as the most fundamental powers of this realm, law powers are extremely profound, and there will sometimes be certain connections between certain law powers. When some compatible law powers are used alongside one another, they'll be able to significantly enhance each other," Mo Yu explained.

"So you're saying that some laws can be used in combination with one another?" Han Li asked.

"That's right, but it's a very rare occurrence, and not all law powers are compatible with one another. Only the law powers that are a good fit with each other have a chance of achieving resonance, such as the laws of yin and yang, the laws of wind and fire, you get the idea," Mo Yu replied.

"I see. In that case, my laws of time had to have somehow combined with Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3's law powers just now, and that resulted in an elevation of both of our law powers," Han Li mused.

"According to my knowledge, it's very difficult to combine law powers like this, and even for those who possess theoretically compatible law powers, it still takes extensive practice to facilitate resonance of law powers like this. Up to this point, Fellow Daoist Li have only met several times, and we've never practiced combining our law powers in the past, so how did this just spontaneously happen all of a sudden?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"As I mentioned, all law powers are extremely profound, and I daresay even a dao lord doesn't have full understanding over the laws that they've mastered. As for spontaneous law resonance, this is not something that hasn't happened before, so there's no need to be alarmed. If I'm not mistaken, you're cultivating the laws of reincarnation, right? I must admit, it's extremely rare to see resonance take place between two of the three paramount laws," Mo Yu mused.

Wyrm 3 didn't seem to be very convinced by this explanation, but she didn't say press any further on this subject.

Meanwhile, Han Li turned to Wyrm 3 with a hint of surprise in his eyes.

Prior to this, he hadn't been able to identify what law powers Wyrm 3 had been using, but Mo Yu had just answered that question for him.

"Both of your requests have been fulfilled now. The two of us have only just returned to this realm, and we still have many things to do, so this is where we'll part ways. I'll send the two of you out of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor soon. In the meantime, please wait here for a moment," Lu Yuqing said, then swept a hand through the air.

Before Han Li and Wyrm 3 had a chance to respond, a burst of azure light swept up both her and Mo Yu before flying away into the distance, vanishing out of sight in a flash.

Han Li looked on at the departing duo with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Even though he had been skeptical about some of the things that the soul fragment had told him, never could he have imagined that he would be a Gray Immortal. As for Lu Yuqing, he certainly would've never guessed that she was the reincarnation of the Boundless Daoist and the true Infernal Frost Immortal Lord.

However, what came as the biggest surprise to him was that Mo Yu and the Infernal Frost Immortal Lord seemed to have become dao partners countless years ago.

Fate was truly a fickle and whimsical mistress at times.

As these thoughts were flashing through his mind, he turned to take a glance at Wyrm 3, and he couldn't see her expression through her mask, but it seemed that she was in deep thought.

He directed his gaze away from her, then descended onto the collapsed palace down below before releasing his spiritual sense.

Before long, an elated look appeared on his face as he swept a sleeve through the air to release several streaks of azure light in all directions, and the streaks of light quickly carried some objects back to him, namely a few pieces of the shattered golden roof and two destroyed golden puppets.

The roof had been constructed out of some type of golden material with a series of spirit patterns engraved onto its surface, and these roof fragments were giving off a type of special aura that was rather similar to that of his Integrated Five Extremes Mountain.

The golden roof had shown itself to be extremely effective in warding off pill tribulations earlier, and even though it had been shattered, these fragments still retained their spiritual nature, so they were still very useful to him.

As for the two puppets, he was quite interested in them as well.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 remained still on the spot, displaying no intention to scour the palace to spoils.

Han Li quickly stowed these things away, yet right as he was about to keep searching, a thick pillar of golden light suddenly descended out of the sky without any warning, encompassing both of them in the blink of an eye.

Han Li felt the air constrict around him, and there was tremendous pressure surging out of the golden light, instantly rendering him completely immobilized.

Countless runes were surging incessantly throughout the golden light, then converged toward Han Li's duo to form a pair of golden arrays.

Both of them felt the entirety of their fields of view being completely filled with golden radiance, following which they abruptly vanished from within the pillar of golden light.

......

Elsewhere in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, there stood a relatively well-preserved three-story pagoda in a garden that was overgrown with weeds.

Two people were standing on the top floor of the pagoda, and both of them were looking into the distance.

They were none other than Mo Yu and Lu Yuqing, and the former had his arms wrapped around the latter as he gently stroked her shoulder.

"You're a lot more petite than before. I wasn't able to embrace you like this in the past," Mo Yu chuckled.

"Oh? It sounds like you like this body of mine better than my previous one," Lu Yun remarked as she raised an eyebrow.

Mo Yu's expression instantly stiffened upon seeing this, and cold sweat began to bead up on his forehead as he hurriedly replied, "Your appearance isn't important, what's important to me is what's on the inside!"

Chapter 512: Parting Ways

"I can't be bothered beating you anymore. It's a waste of my energy," Lu Yun scoffed.

"You're completely right. My skin is really thick, so it doesn't really hurt me, but if you hurt your hand while beating me, then I could never forgive myself," Mo Yu said with a wide grin.

"Do you really not blame me for what I did all those years ago?" Lu Yun asked as she stepped out of Mo Yu's embrace and made her way over to the railing in front of her.

"The first few centuries after you sealed me away, I was indeed quite angry and confused, and after that, I even came to resent you a little. However, as more time passed, I simply missed you and couldn't work up the desire to resent you any longer," Mo Yu replied.

"I didn't think that the Reincarnation Palace would react so aggressively, to the point that they attacked my Infernal Frost Immortal Manor. The situation completely spiraled out of control from there, and the Heavenly Court ended up becoming the main beneficiary," Lu Yun sighed.

"It's alright, it's all in the past... Now that we've returned to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, it's time that we settled the score with the Heavenly Court," Mo Yu said as he reached out to stroke Lu Yun's shoulder once again.

A loud slap rang out as the back of the hand was dealt a heavy blow.

"Don't go touching me as you please when there are other people watching!" Lu Yun scolded with her back facing Mo Yu, but there was a faint smile playing on her lips.

......

In the sky above a vast, nameless ocean.

Countless streaks of light suddenly erupted out thin air, then converged to form a rectangular door of light that was several dozen feet tall and giving off bursts of formidable spatial fluctuations.

The radiant golden light within the door of light flashed momentarily, following which a pillar of golden light erupted out from within. A pair of figures were sent flying out of the door of light alongside the golden pillar, following which the door of light quickly faded away.

The two figures were none other than Wyrm 3 and Han Li, both of whom had already adopted their disguises once again.

Not long after they parted ways with Mo Yu and Lu Yun, they were teleported out of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor.

After taking a moment to steady himself, Han Li looked around with a slightly lost expression as he asked, "Do you know where we are right now, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3?"

Wyrm 3 flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip that contained a map, and after inspecting the map for a moment to ascertain their location, she replied, "We're still in the Black Wind Sea right now, but we're very far away from Red Moon Island."

"Would I be able to have a look at that map?" Han Li asked.

"It's not worth much anyway, so you can have it. In any case, I most likely won't be coming back to the Black Wind Sea ever again," Wyrm 3 said as she casually tossed the jade slip at Han Li.

Han Li caught the jade slip, then cupped her fist toward her in a grateful salute.

"Do you have any plans from here, Fellow Daoist Han?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"I still have some private matters to take care of in the Black Wind Sea. After that, I'll probably be leaving the Black Wind Sea as well," Han Li replied.

"Just leaving the Black Wind Sea most likely isn't going to be enough. My advice to you is that you should leave the Northern Glacial Immortal Region altogether," Wyrm 3 said.

"That was my intention further down the line. Once news of Xiao Jinhan and Gongshu Jiu's demise reach the Heavenly Court, the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Realm is most likely going to undergo an enormous change. Those of us who have entered the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor will surely be targeted by the Heavenly Court, and that's not to mention that I'm already a wanted fugitive of the Immortal Palace," Han Li mused.

Even though he had managed to slay Gongshu Jiu in the immortal manor, there had been a huge element of luck in that battle.

If he were to unleash all of his most powerful abilities at once, then he really did possess the power required to slay a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal, but the problem was that his limited immortal spiritual power reserves meant that he wouldn't be able to maintain this peak form for very long.

If it weren't for the fact that Gongshu Jiu had already been significantly worn down by Mo Yu and the resonance that had taken place between his and Wyrm 3's spirit domains, there was no way that he would've been able to secure that victory.

He was definitely going to be hunted by Heavenly Court immortal envoys of comparable cultivation base from this point onward, and the thought of that filled him with the burning desire to attain more power. Given the turmoil that was inevitably going to sweep through the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, this was clearly not a place where he could continue to cultivate in peace.

"With your unfathomable powers, your future should be a bright one with limitless potential, but in reality, it's one that's fraught with peril, and even the slightest misstep could lead to your demise," Wyrm 3 suddenly said.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he replied, "If you have something to say, then say it. There's no need to try and scare me."

"I'm not trying to scare you, Fellow Daoist Han, I'm merely stating the facts. The fact that you've cultivated both the Spirit Refinement Technique and the laws of time means that your days are most likely numbered," Wyrm 3 said.

"What do you mean by that?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"There are some circumstances involved that I can't explain to you right now, but what I can tell you is that the best way for you to weather this storm is to become a true core member of our Reincarnation Palace. I can submit a recommendation for you if you'd like. Once you have the protection of the Reincarnation Palace, it won't be so easy for the Heavenly Court to target you," Wyrm 3 explained.

"Was I not a core member before?" Han Li asked.

"Reincarnation Disciples are supposed to be core members of our Reincarnation Palace, but due to the circumstances, your instatement as a Reincarnation Disciple was quite rushed, so none of the higher-ups of our Reincarnation Palace are aware of your existence," Wyrm 3 replied.

"I'm not completely opposed to the idea, but does the Reincarnation Palace really have the power to oppose the Heavenly Court?" Han Li asked.

"Compared with the Heavenly Court, we don't have any major subsidiary powers on the surface, such as the Immortal Palaces. However, underground organizations like the Ubiquitous Pavilion and the Transient Guild are far more covert, and there are too many such organizations to count littered throughout the entire Immortal Realm. I'm sure you're well aware of the cumulative power of such organizations," Wyrm 3 said.

Han Li fell into deep thought upon hearing this.

The Transient Guild was already an extremely powerful organization on its own, so if it really was just one of the countless subsidiary powers of the Reincarnation Palace, then the Reincarnation Palace would truly be a monolith of unimaginable proportions.

Even so, Han Li still didn't immediately jump to a decision. "I need some time to think about this."

Wyrm 3 had already anticipated this response, and she replied, "That's fine. I'm sure you'll decide to join us one day."

"In any case, it's true that I can't stay in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region any longer. Can you suggest any good ways for me to leave this immortal region?" Han Li asked.

"There are different ways to travel between immortal regions, but the most common method is to use interregion gates. Back when the Northern Glacial Immortal Realm was under the Infernal Frost Immortal Lord's command, there had been a total of eight interregion gates, but most of them have been destroyed since then, and at this point, there's only a single one left. It's under the control of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and it's situated in the Extreme Star Palace."

"Only one? Doesn't that mean that I'll have no choice but to go through the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace if I want to travel to other immortal regions?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"This is the only official route, and of course, it's inaccessible to our Reincarnation Palace, so we've created another avenue through which one can reach the nearest Black Mountain Immortal Region, but it's far more time and energy-consuming than traveling through an interregion gate," Wyrm 3 replied.

"How so?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not sure if you're aware of this, but aside from a very small number of immortal regions that directly neighbor one another, most of them are separated by vast primordial lands. These primordial lands vary in size, but all of them are extremely perilous. Through several million years of exploration, our Reincarnation Palace was able to establish a relatively safe route to the Black Mountain Immortal Region," Wyrm 3 explained.

"Why didn't the Reincarnation Palace just construct an interregion gate of its own? Wouldn't that be much safer and more convenient?" Han Li asked.

"An interregion gate is not just an ordinary super long distance teleportation array, Fellow Daoist Han. The entire teleportation process requires the participation of cultivators who are at or above the Golden Immortal Stage and are adept at using spatial powers. On top of that, an astronomical amount of resources is required to construct the gate, so it's not just something that anyone can afford to construct," Wyrm 3 explained.

"Perhaps that would be a major obstacle for other powers, but surely the Reincarnation Palace possesses more than sufficient wealth to accomplish such a feat," Han Li mused.

"You're right. Given the wealth that our Reincarnation Palace possesses, we could construct even three or four interregion gates in this immortal region with no problems. However, the operation of an interregion gate involves the usage of spatial law powers, and those law power fluctuations are impossible to conceal. Unless we construct the interregion gates but never use them, they'll eventually all be taken over by the Heavenly Court," Wyrm 3 explained.

"I see. In that case, can I access the established route that you just mentioned?" Han Li asked.

"As a Reincarnation Disciple, you have the right to use the route," Wyrm 3 replied with a nod, then flipped a hand over to produce a white jade badge that she tossed at Han Li.

"You can find all of the information pertaining to the route in this jade badge," Wyrm 3 said.

"Why didn't you use this jade badge as leverage to force me to become a core member of the Reincarnation Palace?" Han Li asked as he caught the jade badge.

"There's no need for me to do that. I'm sure you'll willingly make the decision yourself in the near future. Oh, and here's the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique that I promised you earlier," Wyrm 3 said, then flipped her hand over once again to produce another jade slip that she tossed at Han Li.

Han Li caught the black jade slip, then briefly inspected its contents before stowing it away into his storage bracelet.

"I can see that you're a woman of your word, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3. You have my thanks," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

"I still have some other matters to attend to in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so this is where we'll have to part ways," Wyrm 3 said, then immediately turned to depart.

However, she then suddenly turned around again as she continued, "Your cautious nature really reminds me of someone else that I know. If you ever get to meet him someday, I'm sure the two of you would really get along."

After that, she flew away as a streak of light, quickly vanishing into the distance.